<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2016Q3.Global.NUR.1962.PSTN.Email 5a - Whitepaper: Making PSTN migration work</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Are you ready for a post-PSTN world?</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Integration is the key to successful PSTN transformation
Happy New Year! Wishing you all the very best for 2017. Following a short break for the holidays, we’re back with another insight into public switched telephone network (PSTN) transformation. 

In our previous communications, we laid the groundwork with the importance, the benefits and the urgency for moving from PSTN to full-IP services. Now it’s time to get started! The benefits – secure voice revenues, new business opportunities and lower costs – are just a transformation project away. 

But where do you start?
A wide-scale network transformation project like this is hardly business as usual, even with the wealth of experience and expertise you have at your disposal. How do you manage resources and expectations, maintain current services, keep to timeframes and budgets and ensure a successful transformation across your entire network, not just the easy parts? 

From years of experience, Nokia recommends an integrated approach to PSTN transformation. This approach recognizes that PSTN transformation goes way beyond the technical. It must align business strategy with migration project execution and, above all, ensure customers continue to get the quality of service they expect from you. 

White paper: Making PSTN migration work 
In this exclusive white paper, Nokia explains how to make PSTN migration work for you. It covers: 



	- What makes PSTN transformation such a challenge 

	- Why an integrated approach is essential 

	- The 3 steps of a successful PSTN transformation project

	- The value of partnering with a transformation specialist 



Download the white paper today. For more information, contact our team &lt;[[mailto:Eveline.verschraegen@nokia.com]]&gt; or visit the Nokia PSTN Transformation &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/solutions/pstn-smart-transform]]&gt; website.
Connect with us
© 2017 Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
