<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-GEPS TO-Partner-Email-Operational-T001OY.20697.Email - FN FBA pricing update</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>FN POL Europe and MEA Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs update</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
E-bulletin
FN POL Europe and MEA Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs update
Dear Nokia Partners,

Updated FN POL Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs, including POL Configurator, were made available on the Nokia PRM Partner Portal [Account -&gt;Details -&gt; Personal space links -&gt; Partner Pricing folders] end November 2017.
Key Highlights:


	- Generated with updated FN POL EMEA pricing tool ed 6.1 [POL v01P06]. New POL Blue Print 3.0 solution Hardware and Software:











	- Additional options/selections provided in the configurator
	- POL pricelist enabling VAR program
	- New/updated buttons supporting the configurator
	- Introduction of POL Hospitality premium services
	- New 1GE PoE ONT
	- New POL OLT SW license replacing FBA OLT SW license enabling POL functionality
	- Separate spare parts sheet
	- Improved pricing versus POL Blue Print 2.0
	- Modified maintenance pricing approach, introduction of POL small networks pricing
	- Export classification update


Product Notifications:


	- To receive notifications on product updates, manufacture discontinued dates and other product status changes, please subscribe to Notifications in OLCS (Nokia’s on-line customer support website).
	- To receive notifications on partner price catalog updates, please subscribe to Notifications in Partner Portal/Partner Personal space


For more information:

Pricing information is available in Partner Personal folder on the Nokia PRM Partner Portal. Please contact me should you have any questions.

Bogdan Vasilescu
Nokia Global Partner Program and Sales Team
Connect with us
©{{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia | Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
