<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.IPRout.Partner.All.A.G.E.17177.Pricing Updates NAM PRM.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>e-Bulletin:  ION / IP Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs update</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
e-Bulletin: ION / IP Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs update
Dear Partners,

During the week of September 18, 2017 we have updated and published the ION / IP Routing Partner Product and Maintenance Services Price Catalogs. They are available on the Nokia PRM Partner Portal &lt;[[https://nokia.lightning.force.com/lightning/page/home]]&gt;. Please look inside the pricing groups associated with your accounts on the PRM.


	- Key Highlights:
Generated with updated IP Routing pricing tool v1.2.8 [PPP v75]. Includes Hardware and Software updates:











	- We will organize “How to use the latest ION / IP price catalogs” training sessions in October. Invites will be sent shortly.
	- Product Notifications:
To receive notifications on product updates, manufacture discontinued dates and other product status changes, please subscribe to Notifications in OLCS &lt;[[https://support.alcatel-lucent.com/portal/web/support]]&gt; (Nokia’s on-line customer support website). Go to OLCS&gt;MyAccount&gt;ManageSubscriptions&gt;Alerts. To receive notifications on partner price catalog updates, please subscribe to Notifications from within your partners’ Personal spaces.


For more information:
Latest Pricing rules type of information are available, by Route to Market type on the Nokia PRM Partner Portal &lt;[[https://nokia.lightning.force.com/lightning/page/home]]&gt;.
Please contact us should you have any questions.

Bogdan Vasilescu
Nokia Global Partner Program and Sales Team
Connect with us
© 2017 Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
