<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17-GEPS-XLE-Email-SBC for E Nurture-T001ZO.Email 3 Consideration</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Protect business communications and stimulate innovation – today!</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Use Case 

Spur innovation and growth while protecting your network center 
Explosive growth of new devices, data streams and communication protocols is creating huge opportunities for your enterprise. But what’s the best way to take advantage of them? By adopting new technology rapidly and having the power to securely control and manage IP communication streams as they cross your network boundaries.

That’s where the Nokia Enterprise Session Border Controller (SBC) comes in. It helps you protect your network and accelerate innovation by enabling secure use of communications carried over APIs and new protocols like WebRTC. 

Discover how Nokia Enterprise SBC can help your enterprise:


	- Stimulate innovation and growth by using new IP and cloud technologies to support data communications for employees, partners, and customers 

	- Protect your business by controlling data streams, preventing traffic overload and securing your network from external attacks
	- Provide better experiences to customers and employees by providing guaranteed quality for IP-based voice and video services
Enjoy!
Brendan Ziolo
Head of Digital Networks Marketing, Nokia
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; · Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; · Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
