<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-TEPS-Transportation-Email-Innotrans email-T0023S.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Join Nokia at Innotrans 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Make every journey an upgrade
Innotrans 2018 
18-21 September, Messe Berlin
Modern railway systems demand always safe, always on-time, always connected journeys. At Innotrans 2018 discover the latest communications technologies and mission-critical networks that can help you:


	- connect the journey end-to-end for passengers and goods,

	- make on-time a reality while maximizing reliability and efficiency – for systems, passengers, and goods,

	- combat cybersecurity threats in the digital era,

	- build future-proof networks that more easily adapt, so you can benefit from the best technologies available such as LTE, IP/MPLS, DWDM and IoT. 




Visit the Nokia stand to explore these topics and more, and to see how our innovative technologies can help you make every journey an upgrade. 

We look forward to welcoming you at Innotrans and making new connections together, 

Your Nokia team





 &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cEtAjpwOQjk&amp;did=d000000000g7&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;

 

New to our solutions?
Put Nokia’s 30+ years of mission-critical rail communication expertise to work for you. Visit our website &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/transportation/railways?did=d000000000g7&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; and watch a video introduction &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cEtAjpwOQjk&amp;did=d000000000g7&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; of our rail technologies
Looking for more on what we will feature at Innotrans 2018?
Stay tuned to your e-mail for updated information on our demos, or see the latest information on our InnoTrans 2018 event site. &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/innotrans?did=d000000000g7&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Karaportti 3, 02610 Espoo, Finland 
Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia’s networks business or its third-party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
