<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Util Crit Comms-Util Architecture-Email-SIEW2018 Invite-T002DG.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Communication innovations for new business models at SIEW</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Singapore International Energy Week (SIEW)


30 October – 02 November 2018
Marina Bay Sands, Singapore
Join us at SIEW 2018
SIEW was first held in 2008 organized by the Singapore Energy Market Authority (EMA). This event is an annual platform for energy professionals, policymakers and commentators to discuss and share best practices and solutions within the global energy space. Last year, there were &gt;11000 delegates from &gt;70 continents.
Now on its 10th year, SIEW 2018 has the theme “Transforming Energy: Invest, Innovate Integrate”. Hear global energy leaders and experts share insights on our energy future, and engage with leaders in the energy community from government, industry, and heads of international organizations.
Meet us at Delegate Lounge on Level 4
Nokia will be present the entire 4 days at the Delegate lounge on Level 4, with a dedicated area for conversations. We will be very keen to meet you, discuss challenges, projects, and share our vision on advanced grid communications and analytics, as well as how we facilitate utilities transition to new business models as a next generation utility.
Martin Hauske, Asia Pacific Energy Segment Sales Leader at Nokia, will be speaking at the International Energy Agency (IEA) Forum on 31 October, under the Panel2 Managing Transformation - what are the risks and how can we build resilience? &lt;[[https://www.siew.sg/siew-2018/events/singapore---iea-forum]]&gt;
For more information on Nokia solutions for the energy industry, visit our webpage &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/energy-resources]]&gt;.

We look forward to seeing you in Singapore!
SIEW 2018: https://www.siew.sg/home &lt;[[https://www.siew.sg/home]]&gt;
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
