<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-TEPS-Transportation-Email-Airport Dubai-T0021D.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Be our guest at Dubai Airport Show on 7-9 May</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Prioritizing safety and security in every connection
Be our guest at Dubai Airport Show
7-9 May 
Dubai World Trade Center, Booth 6200


The Aviation industry is facing continuous growth and stakeholders will need to put in place strategies to address this in the most efficient and cost-effective way. 

Nokia creates the technology to connect the world with sophisticated solutions that are intuitive to use. We listen to your future needs and we help shape your Airport and ATM future based on a clear view of technology opportunities and constraints. 

Our experts will be on site to discuss your requirements and demonstrate our latest innovative products, solutions and services. Nokia is your trusted partner in ensuring the mission-critical communications for the Aviation industry. 
Let’s meet in this exciting conference sessions on “Critical Communication Solutions harnessing new network strategies” on May 8. Speakers: Richard van Wijk and Mervyn Harris

Secure your place by registering today: Register now &lt;[[https://registration.n200.com/survey/0qnqkyklkab3e?actioncode=ATEX12&amp;utm_source=nokia&amp;utm_medium=barters-email&amp;utm_campaign=atcf2018_acquisition_visitors_bartersemail]]&gt;

Nokia is your trusted partner in ensuring the mission-critical 
communication system foundation for a smart, connected airport. 

If you wish to stay updated with the latest Nokia Aviation solutions, please visit our airports 
website &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/aviation?did=d000000000co&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; and for any questions contact us &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/how-to-buy?did=d000000000co&amp;utm_campaign=transportation_event&amp;utm_source=email-list-&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;. 

Looking forward to welcoming you at our booth, 
Nokia team
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Karaportti 3, 02610 Espoo, Finland 
Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
