<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Util Crit Comms-Util Architecture-Email-Distrubtech invit-T003I9.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Empowering your new business models – DistribuTECH 2019</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Please join us at DistribuTECH 2019
Empowering your new energy future
February 5-7, 2019
At DistribuTECH 2019 &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/events/calendar/distributech-2019/?did=d0000000018z&amp;utm_campaign=util_architecture&amp;utm_source=email-list-marketo&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;, join us to experience how your business can benefit from a new energy communications architecture. Learn about the latest developments from Bell Labs, and how you can use your Future X power utility architecture to boost control, innovation and take advantage of new business models.
Discover how:


	- Analytics applications can help you maximize value from your processes, people and assets.
	- The latest Private LTE network options can improve your critical distribution grid connections for renewables integration and automation, and for your large wind farms.
	- The Nokia Bell Labs Future X architecture for power utilities provides a strategy for renewables integration, automation and new business models.
	- Trans-continental test lab capabilities, from the University of Strathclyde and Nokia, can help you access the latest industry use cases, effectively manage transformation risk and tune new technologies to your business.


We look forward to working with you at DistribuTECH 2019, as we discuss how to empower your new energy future with greater automation and business results.
Visit with Nokia at booth 12133.
Empowered for the new energy future.
Register for DistribuTECH today &lt;[[http://www.nokia.com/about-us/events/calendar/distributech-2019/?did=d0000000018z&amp;utm_campaign=util_architecture&amp;utm_source=email-list-marketo&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;.

 Ernest N. Morial Convention Center
 New Orleans, LA
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
