<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18.IPRout.Energy.Utility.D.N.E.20531.Distributech 2018 Eblast 2.Invite</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Be our guest at DistribuTECH 2018 - January 23-25, San Antonio</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Be our Guest at DistribuTECH 2018
January 23 - 25, 2018
 Henry B. Gonzalez Convention Center
 San Antonio, TX
 Booth #3335
Looking to accelerate your digital transformation?


	- Discover our new Energy Innovation Center capabilities for POC testing with numerous use cases to minimize transformation risk.
	- Learn about the AT&amp;T and Nokia private LTE network solution and benefits of IP/MPLS paired with LTE for M2M/IoT through a live demonstration using AT&amp;T commercial LTE service.
	- Experience a live, converged IP/MPLS, optical, packet microwave network with GOOSE messaging for secure, reliable grid communications.
	- Learn how to automate and exceed NERC CIP compliance, provide a secure end-to-end cyber environment for growing operational networks, and see how management capabilities simplify operations.



Plan to attend an exciting conference session featuring a presentation on private LTE networks

 Real utility experiences optimizing Hybrid FAN communications – (#D0444) 
Wednesday, Jan 24, 10:00 – 11:30 am, Room 208.

 Attend DistribuTECH courtesy of Nokia. Get complimentary access to the exhibition hall, keynote session, and networking party.

 To get your free floor pass, go to www.distributech.com &lt;[[http://www.distributech.com/]]&gt;. Click on Register, select Rates, and then Visitor (Exhibition only). At the bottom left of the registration summary, enter in the promotional/source code field: DTPASS18, and press apply.

 For more information on Nokia solutions, visit our webpage &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/power-utilities/smart-grid]]&gt;.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
