<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Partners TO-SPIF Communications-Email-Optical LAN SPIF-T00283.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Sales Performance Incentive Program Optical LAN</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Dear Partner,

Nokia is happy to announce an exciting new Sales Performance Incentive program we will be offering October 1, 2018 through December 31, 2019 for our Optical LAN (formerly POL) solution. With this incentive program, your sales representatives will earn reward points to redeem for prizes for registered, approved and closed Nokia Optical LAN deals.

You will receive additional program details in the coming weeks but to help you prepare now, please refer to the eligibility criteria below.

 Eligibility requirements:
To participate in this rewards program, the following basic conditions must be met: 

 	- Signed PPA contract in place 	- Accreditation level (Direct Reseller either Advanced or Expert in Nokia Optical LAN; Distributor at Premier level) 	- Sales representatives certified on Optical LAN technology 

 
Becoming Sales certified is easy so if you haven’t yet met that condition, you can get started today by accessing the Partner Learning Store &lt;[[https://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489518527001]]&gt;. The training is online, and free! 

 For questions or assistance, please contact your Nokia Partner Sales Manager. 

 Jerome Jullien 
 VP Nokia Global Partner Program
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia’s networks business or its third-party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
