<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.BBAccess.FTTx.none.L.N.N.12814.FTTx campaign for US regionals.C3 - Helping yo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Learn the secrets of the best broadband providers</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
You&apos;ve chosen your technology &lt;[[https://pages.nokia.com/Fiber.strategies.broadband1.html]]&gt;. You’ve developed your business case &lt;[[https://pages.nokia.com/Fiber.strategies.broadband2.html]]&gt; with robust financial modeling. Now it’s time to choose your partner for deploying ultra-broadband services. 

In this white paper, learn why Nokia is right for you.
Your investment needs to last well into the future. So it makes sense to select a partner that can stay with you for the long-run, no matter which technology you choose today, and wherever you may go tomorrow. 

Download this white paper &lt;[[https://pages.nokia.com/fiber.strategies.broadband3.html]]&gt; from Nokia, the last in a 3-part series, to discover why we are:


	- Trusted to provide more than 50% of all fixed broadband connections in North America.
	- Trusted by 18 of the 20 biggest broadband operators in the world.
	- Trusted by some of North America’s best independent operators, including EPB Chattanooga, LUS Fiber, Bristol Tennessee, Frontier Communications, the City of Opelika, and many others.


Nokia is the only vendor in North America able to provide and support a full-breadth of fiber, copper, cable and mobile ultra-broadband technologies. That means we’re technology-agnostic, so we can advise on and support the long-term evolution of your network without privileging any single solution.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
