<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-TEPS-Public Sector-Email-APCO Email Invite-T0026B.Email 2</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Is your command center ready for the multimedia era?</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Come to Nokia Booth at APCO 2018
Is your command center ready to gather, analyze and correlate rich multimedia information and to turn it into actionable decisions?
APCO exhibition: August 06 - 07, 2018, Las Vegas, NV
We have a limited quantity of Free registration passes available. Register early to confirm your pass and also to reserve a demo tour.
The upcoming internet of saving lives things and associated real-time multimedia services will dramatically increase the volume of information sent to city command centers. Time is coming to prepare for this new era, and make sure all this information can be properly analyzed to facilitate and accelerate the decision making process of command centers.
Visit Nokia booth #1841 to experience next generation command center and discuss with us how to get the best of this digital evolution.
Reserve your spot by completing our online form and visit our booth to win a Nokia Steel activity and sleep watch!
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; · Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; · Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia’s networks business or its third-party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
