<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17-GEPS TO-Service Provider-Email-BPS eDM-T001OT.II.Email_c_EMEA non DE/AT follo</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Reminder: Share your Cable Industry insight for charity</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
Reminder: Share your Cable Industry insight for charity
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=edit me}}, 

I reached out to you recently to invite you to take part in a short survey about technology solutions for Cable Operators. If you have responded, many thanks! If not, there is still time and we value your insight. 

The survey is being conducted by an independent third party on behalf of Nokia and should take around 10 minutes. All opinions you offer will remain anonymous and confidential. The results will be used, in aggregate, to improve Nokia’s products and services and the way we work with our customers overall. 

In return for your participation, a donation of $30 (or the equivalent in local currency) will be made to a charity that you will be able to select on completion of the survey. The charities you can choose from are: UNICEF (United Nations Children’s Fund), Médecins Sans Frontières (Doctors Without Borders), WWF (World Wildlife Fund), and OXFAM (Famine Relief).

Please CLICK HERE &lt;[[{{lead.mkto_Temp String:default=edit me}}]]&gt; to take the survey now.

Thank you in advance for your participation. We value your opinion. 
 
Steve Davidson
Cable Customer Marketing Lead, Europe
https://insight.nokia.com/users/steve-Davidson &lt;[[https://insight.nokia.com/users/steve-Davidson]]&gt;

 If you would prefer to not take part in the research please email news.networks@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:news.networks@nokia.com]]&gt;
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
