<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Railways-RailIOTDG-Email-RailLive19email-T003M2.Invitation Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Travel at the speed of life - at RailLive - Bilbao, Spain</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Join us at Rail Live and experience how your business can travel at the speed of life.
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=customer}},
Rail Live promises to be the epicenter of supply chain innovation and technology for the rail industry in 2019.
This year, Nokia will share new automation capabilities designed to help you achieve the full opportunities and benefits of industrial IoT and advanced analytics.
Rail Live, March 5-7, 2019 – Bilbao Exhibition Center, Bilbao, Spain &lt;[[https://www.terrapinn.com/exhibition/asia-pacific-rail/index.stm]]&gt;
We look forward to meeting with you at the conference and at the Nokia stand (#40B) where our technology experts are ready to discuss how your operations can benefit from predictive maintenance, intelligent asset management, operational intelligence and new levels of cybersecurity.
During the conference presentation sessions, please join Karsten Oberle, Nokia Global Railway practice lead, in the Digital and IoT stream, March 6th at 15:45 for an informative session on Automation in rail - Improving rail operations efficiently.
You are also invited to join Karsten at a roundtable discussion entitled Are you ready for automation in rail – opportunities and challenges, March 6th at 11:20.
We look forward to seeing you at Rail Live 2019 and meeting with you at our stand. If you would like to schedule a private briefing, please contact your Nokia account representative.

 Best regards,

 The Nokia Railway Solutions Team

 For information about Nokia railway solutions, visit 
https://networks.nokia.com/industries/railways &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/industries/railways?did=d000000001b9&amp;utm_campaign=railiotdg&amp;utm_source=email-list-raillive&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=invitation&amp;utm_term=railiotdg]]&gt;
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
