<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18.InterTraffic-Eblast.SR1801021585EN.Email 01-</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Be our guest at Intertraffic 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Critical communications for safe, on time and connected journeys
Efficiency today, flexibility for the future
Be our guest at Intertraffic 2018
20th March – 23rd March 2018, Intertraffic Amsterdam, Hall 8, booth #08.622

 Nokia is pleased to invite you to join the leading exhibition for the traffic and mobility industry in Amsterdam.

Stop by our booth #08.622 in Hall 8 Smart Mobility area to meet our experts and discover Nokia 
intelligent highway solutions for safe, on-time and connected journeys. We invite you to see our demos:



	- Optimize highway communication networks: Learn how to benefit from a smooth migration path from legacy technologies to a converged communications network supporting all Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS) on highways.
	- Prepare for the future of mobility: Get to know our C-V2X and roadside cloud solutions for vehicle-to-everything (V2X), analytics for automated driving and traveler infotainment.


Plan to attend our presentation in the Smart Mobility Theatre 2 (Hall 8) on Wednesday, 21st March from 11:00 to 11:45: “The future of connected mobility: beyond autonomous horses&quot;.

Registration here &lt;[[http://go.nokia.com/NR008W0V000b04Z0TU0003S]]&gt; to the event is free of charge. 

For more information on Nokia solutions for intelligent highways, visit our webpage &lt;[[http://go.nokia.com/iN4W0URb02S00V000003Z00]]&gt;.

Look for us in Amsterdam
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
