<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Railways-RailCritComm DG-Email-APACRail19email-T003M1.Invitation Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>See the latest in rail innovations in action at Asia Pacific Rail, March 19-20, 2019, Hong Kong</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Dear {{lead.First Name:default=customer}},
We hope to see you at Asia Pacific Rail 2019, a premier event that highlights the latest innovations and technologies for the Rail industry. Nokia is pleased to participate again this year and would like to invite you to visit our stand (#E25) as we showcase new automation capabilities and demonstrate how digital railways can benefit from the latest networking advances, industrial IoT and advanced analytics solutions.
Asia Pacific Rail, March 19-20, 2019 – Hong Kong Convention and Exhibition Center &lt;[[https://www.terrapinn.com/exhibition/asia-pacific-rail/index.stm]]&gt;
Join us for discussions on:
Predictive Maintenance: Learn how Nokia’s IoT-based solution can help you optimize asset utilization and control maintenance cost. Our advanced analytics can assess the operating conditions of trackside and rolling stock assets and automate scheduling of maintenance work orders.
Smart Stations: Explore new IoT connectivity, operations center and advanced analytics solutions and see how they can come together to intelligently secure, automate and optimize stations – delivering new value and safety for your customers and better economics for your operation.
Intelligent Management of MPLS Networks: Understand how the Nokia NSP enables you to manage network infrastructure proficiently and with high agility. Learn how this secure, proven software platform with simple template-driven provisioning, and proactive end-to-end performance monitoring can ensure your industrial applications are available, and how it uses advanced intelligence to pinpoint emerging issues before they impact your operations.
We look forward to seeing you at Asia Pacific Rail 2019 and exploring how Nokia can help your railway - travel at the speed of life.

 Best regards,

 The Nokia Railway Solutions Team

 For more information on Nokia railway solutions, visit 
https://networks.nokia.com/industries/railways &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/industries/railways?did=d000000001ba&amp;utm_campaign=railcritcomm_dg&amp;utm_source=email-list-apacrail&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=invitation&amp;utm_term=railcritcommdg]]&gt;
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
