<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokCorp.Partner.All.T.G.E.16195.Partner Newsletter 2017 September.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Nokia Global Partner Program Newsletter for September</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Partner Newsletter | September 2017
Program News
Nokia advances an important step forward to become a digital company with PRM


Earlier this month, Nokia launched the Partner Relationship Management system, or PRM. This new PRM tool provides partners and Nokia sales teams with one single place to connect for all your sales needs, resulting in greater efficiency and real time collaboration. If you missed any of the PRM webcasts or training, access the resource links below, or contact your partner sales manager if you have questions or need assistance. 

Resources: 
PRM Go Live Training &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/ka241000000Nd16AAC/PRM-Training]]&gt;
Intro to PRM System (recorded webcast)  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06941000003GgPt]]&gt;
PRM Starter Kit &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06841000003ZKxg]]&gt;



Featured Products
Cloud scale routing for Internet evolution


Watch Nokia’s President of IP/Optical Networks, Basil Alwan, share his insights on what he believes will be the biggest changes to the network and how cloud-scale routing will play a major role in addressing them. 
Watch video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLgKNvl454BxcnC6hK6so8rYDdC-kShqQY]]&gt;


 

Innovations on the new Nokia 7750 SR-s series


Reimagine your IP networks with the new FP4 powered 7750 SR-s series. Ken Kutzler, Nokia Vice President, General Manager, IP Hardware Business shares why the latest IP routing innovations delivers unprecedented scale, security and capability without compromise. 
Watch video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XZuyyt3tQmM&amp;index=2&amp;list=PLgKNvl454BxcnC6hK6so8rYDdC-kShqQY]]&gt;


Nuage Networks Enterprise Solution


In this latest interview with Mike Loomis, Global Sales Leader Extra-large enterprises, learn what’s new in Nokia’s offering in the Enterprise space and how Nuage Networks has been a driver behind the success. 
Watch video  &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ucwzTWxqQ24&amp;list=PLgKNvl454BxcnC6hK6so8rYDdC-kShqQY&amp;index=4]]&gt;



Success Stories
Nokia leading Optical Network Innovation


Highlights from Dell&apos;Oro Group and Ovum show strong Nokia progress: 



	- Worldwide #1 position in 200G port shipments 

	- #1 in Optical Networking in Europe with 26% market share

	- #1 in Optical Networking in the group of the 5 biggest European economies (Germany, UK, France, Italy and Spain), with 33% market share; 10 points ahead of second-ranking vendor 

	- #1 in Datacenter Interconnect application in Europe, Middle East and Africa, with 35% market share 



Nokia to supply mission-critical communications network to the County of Fresno, California to enhance public safety


Nokia is modernizing the communications network of the County of Fresno, California to strengthen emergency response capabilities and enhance public safety. Nokia will upgrade the network using microwave packet radio and Internet Protocol/Multi-protocol Label Switching (IP/MPLS) technology, which will provide secure, resilient and reliable data links for first responders and County facilities. 

Read press release &lt;[[http://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/releases/2017/07/20/nokia-to-supply-mission-critical-communications-network-to-the-county-of-fresno-california-to-enhance-public-safety]]&gt;



Success stories planned for Q4 


Success stories will soon be available on the PRM Portal as Powerpoint slide decks that include speaker notes to help you position Nokia products and solutions with your customers. The following areas will be covered: 



	- Transportation 

	- Public Safety 

	- Oil, Gas, &amp; Mining 

	- Utilities 

	- Passive Optical LAN (POL) 



In the meantime, here is our Creos case study in the smart grid space. 




Campaigns


Lead gen campaigns 


As a reminder, we have several off-the-shelf campaigns available for partners: 



	- Data Center Interconnect (DCI) 

	- MPLS for Railways 

	- IP/MPLS for Mission Critical Applications 

	- Passive Optical LAN (POL) 

	- More than Moving Light … and more



Visit the Co-Marketing Platform &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/ka241000000NcswAAC/Tools]]&gt; on the Partner Portal, or contact your partner sales manager to get started today. 

Next month, we are announcing a new lead generation campaign for partners. You won’t want to miss this one so stay tuned for the Nokia campaign that will redefine private optical networks for the enterprise. In the meantime, join us on October 3, 2017 for our webcast to learn more. Enterprise private optical networks webcast &lt;[[https://event.webcasts.com/starthere.jsp?ei=1162760&amp;tp_key=c5a80170ce&amp;sti=nokia]]&gt;.



Marketing

Your most frequently asked questions now answered


As a member of the Nokia Global Partner Program, from time to time you may have questions related to operations, where to find various tools and resources, how to access training, or perhaps who to contact for support. This page serves as a guide for answering your most frequently asked questions and will be refreshed regularly. 
FAQ page &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/ka241000000Nd3MAAS/FAQs]]&gt;




New IP Transformation for Utilities content 
 

Find valuable portal content (white papers, presentations, sales guide) to use in your communications with customers. 
IP Transformation for Utilities. &lt;[[http://go.nokia.com/L003ZR0060tT0WY000S0V0U]]&gt;




Training
Partner Training &amp; Certification


NokiaEDU recently released the August 2017 Global Partner Program Learning &amp; Certification catalog. Now may be a good time to see what’s new, complete important certifications, or grow your knowledge in a wealth of areas related to Nokia products, solutions, and industries. 

Please visit the Partner Portal to download the following NEW training materials: 
Learning &amp; Certification catalog &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06941000001uTBkAAM]]&gt; – comprehensive training catalog and guide. 
Curriculum updates &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06841000003YQeh]]&gt; – chart showing classes that have been updated for individuals who want to stay current. 
APAC Open enrollment classes  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06841000002rnAo]]&gt;– for IP, Optics, Microwave, POL, Nuage and more. 
EMEA Open sessions &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06841000003Yfwq]]&gt; – for IP, Optics, Microwave, POL, Nuage and more. 



Videos


Telia Finland share why they chose to deploy an SD-WAN solution from Nuage Networks


Listen to Arto Urataipale, Business Program Lead, Telia Finland, talk about their business and provide an overview of the challenges they have with current business services. Arto will then share why they decided to go with an SD-WAN service based on the Nuage Networks Virtualized Network Services. 
Watch customer testimonial  &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=UJUAaaF9TCs]]&gt;

Public backhauling for public safety


In Germany, the central public safety agency of the second largest state has decided to move towards a packet based backhauling solution with the 9500 Microwave Packet Radio from Nokia, to meet their stringent requirements while opening the door to new significant data and broadband applications. 
Watch video &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P2rI_D8nJKU&amp;feature=youtu.be]]&gt;
Read case study  &lt;[[https://resources.ext.nokia.com/asset/193189]]&gt;



Spotlights


Redington Value joins Nokia Global Partner Program


According to the President at Redington Value, Ramkumar Balakrishnan, the company has partnered with Nokia, as it constantly innovates and its leadership in IP/Optical Networks, SDN, FTTx and mobile networks will help drive success for Redington Value’s resellers and their customers. “Our strong partnership will help them build large-scale, carrier-grade IP/Optical infrastructure for web-scale companies, and mission-critical solutions for public sector players, public safety agencies, smart cities, transportation organisations, energy and tech-centric enterprise customers – to name a few,” he added.

 Read press release &lt;[[http://www.channelpostmea.com/2017/07/12/redington-value-joins-nokia-global-partner-program/#F5svDGgXC1pmhT4q.99]]&gt;


Partner Roadshows are a hit!


At our recent roadshows in Munich and Paris, partners had the chance to broaden their knowledge about the Nokia Global Enterprise and Public Sector (GEPS) partner business strategy, receive important updates on the Global Partner Program and its tools, participate in top-level presentations on Nokia’s new solutions and current market trends … and more.


Paris Roadshow attendees trained at Atelier Du Vin Francais for a Molecular Cooking Class and Degustation.


Munich Roadshow attendees hear from Nokia leadership to learn more about the GEPS partner business strategy.


Events


Broadband World Forum, October 24 – 26, Berlin &lt;[[https://tmt.knect365.com/bbwf/]]&gt; 
Join us at Broadband World Forum 2017, booth E104, to discover how our innovations allow you to unleash new possibilities of digital life for your customers. Engage with our experts to learn how Nokia can deliver new services and experiences that will enhance your customers’ business and create a better connected world. 


Other events:


European Utility Week &lt;[[http://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/european-utility-week]]&gt;, 03 – 05 Oct, Amsterdam, Netherlands 
SDN NFV World Congress World Forum &lt;[[http://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/sdn-nfv-world-congress]]&gt;, 09 – 13 Oct, The Hague, Netherlands 
Africom 2017 &lt;[[http://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/africacom-2017]]&gt;, 07 – 09 Nov, Cape Town, South Africa
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
