<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2016Q3.Global.NUR.1962.PSTN.Email 3 - Whitepaper: Unlocking the value in legacy</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Give your PSTN a new voice</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Are you ready for new PSTN opportunities?
Your public switched telephone network (PSTN) services are a vital element of your business. But the technology that underpins these services is old. In fact, most equipment vendors have announced end-of-life for their PSTN portfolios and maintenance contracts by 2020, if not before. 

What happens then? 

The PSTN is reborn as a full-IP network, bringing a host of benefits and opportunities. Transforming the PSTN safeguards and then builds upon your voice revenues but also creates significant operational efficiencies, providing for the future needs of your customers and your business. 

White paper: Unlocking the value in legacy PSTNs
In this exclusive Nokia white paper, we explain the key principles behind PSTN transformation: 




	- The market, technology and business drivers making PSTN transformation a priority today


	- The costs that can be saved and how they combine to make a compelling business case 


	- How PSTN transformation brings new opportunities that increase customer loyalty and revenues 


	- 3 different PSTN transformation techniques that can be used for different segments of your customer base



Download the white paper today. For more information, contact our team &lt;[[mailto:Eveline.verschraegen@nokia.com]]&gt; or visit the Nokia PSTN Transformation &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/solutions/pstn-smart-transform]]&gt; website. 

.
Connect with us
© 2016 Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
