<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CustomField xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <fullName>Guidance__c</fullName>
    <externalId>false</externalId>
    <formula>IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7750SRa&apos;,&quot;Please select the SR-a chassis you require (4 or 8 slots).On this tab also select the number of IOMs,the power supplies and redundancy requirements.Then please select line cards,pluggable optics,licenses and accessories on the subsequent tabs.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7705SARAAx&apos;,&quot;Please select one of the SAR-A/Ax options and choose the appropriate power supply and plug suitable for the installation location. Please select pluggable optics, software licenses and other accessories on the subsequent tabs.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7210SAS-K&apos;,&quot;Please choose the required SAS-K type and whether you require an ETR (Extended Temperature Range) version.Please also decide which combination of power supplies you require and the type of plug appropriate for your implementation.Please select pluggable optics,software licenses and other accessories on the subsequent tabs.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;ISAMFXP&apos;,&apos;Depending on the SW Package to be used a license is needed.Besides the mandatory licenses already selected,please select the licenses needed&apos;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7210SAS-R&apos;,&quot;Please select the power and switch/control plane redundancy required.Once complete please choose the line cards,pluggable optics,software licenses and other accessories on the subsequent tabs.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7705SARH&apos;,&quot;The user should select if they require the high or low voltage version and whether they require Conformal Coating.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7210SAS-MXP&apos;,&quot;Please choose whether you require an ETR (Extended Temperature Range) or non-ETR version.&quot;,IF((Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode== &apos;POLNAR&apos;||Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;POL&apos;),&quot;To be able to walk you through a guided configuration please provide: 1. The number of GPON subscribers (ONTs) to be supported, the Tab &apos;ONT&apos; will allow you to split the number of GPON subscribers to be supported in different ONT types and quantities.2. The Split Ratio that will be used in the Outside Plant for splitting the GPON fiber from the Central Office until the end users. 3. If type B Protection is required (Yes/No)4.If Network redundancy is required (Yes/No)&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode ==&apos;FBANAR&apos;|| Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode ==&apos;FBAOUTSIDENAR&apos;,&quot;To be able to walk you through a guided configuration please provide:1.The number of PON subscribers (ONTs) to be supported, the Tab &apos;ONT&apos; will allow you to split the number of PON subscribers to be supported in different ONT types and quantity. 2.The number of PON Ports needed. Depending on the customers input the number of PON ports needed can be calculated using the Split Ratio, or can be provided directly in the number of PON ports input field. 3.the number of Point-2-Point Subscribers to be supported. 4.If type B Protection is required (Yes/No). 5.If Network redundancy is required (Yes/No)&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;7705SARWWx&apos;,&quot;7705 SAR-W and 7705 SAR-Wx are IP/MPLS based, environment- and climate-hardened, routers designed for communications in outdoor locations.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode==&apos;7705SARHC&apos;,&quot;SAR-Hc provides industry-leading IP/MPLS communications capabilities in a DIN rail-mountable compact form factor with temperature, electromagnetic,shock and vibration hardening.&quot;,&quot;Guidance text&quot;)))))))))))</formula>
    <label>Guidance</label>
    <required>false</required>
    <trackTrending>false</trackTrending>
    <type>Text</type>
    <unique>false</unique>
</CustomField>
