<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<CustomField xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <fullName>Guidance_7705_SAR_O__c</fullName>
    <description>Nokia NPI 7705 SAR O , 7210 SAS T, 7363 ISAM MX-6, 7705 SAR 8, MPW Products Guidance</description>
    <externalId>false</externalId>
    <formula>IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &quot;7705SAR18&quot;,&quot;The SAR-18 is -48v DC powered only. Please select if you require Control Switch Module redundancy and if you require AC power conversion.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &quot;7210SAST&quot;,&quot;Please choose whether you require an ETR (Extended Temperature Range) or non-ETR version of the SAS-T. If you require PoE/PoE+ support then select the 7210 SAS-T ETR variant.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &quot;ISAMFXNAR&quot;,&quot;The 7360 ISAM FX Family can be delivered in different Flavours each supporting a different number of Line termination boards: FX-4 4 LT boards, FX-8 8 LT boards, FX-16 16 LT Boards.For NAR, Shelfs are preconfigured as Starter Kits , Please select the starter kit to be configured.Please also select if the Rack, the AMS or the Layer 3 RTU license need to be included in the cart.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;ISAMFXP&apos;,&quot;Different Network Termination board types exist depending on the switching capacity needed, and whether BITs or non BITs is needed. At least one NT is needed per shelf. Each NT board supports 1 to 4 uplinks. In case of NT-redundancy the number of NTs and uplinks are doubled (paired).Please select if NT-redundancy is needed and which Network Termination board is preferred. You need then to select the uplink SFPs needed.NTIO is supported but optional, each supporting up to 8 uplinks. Please select respective NTIO and uplinks if needed.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;7362DF16GW&apos;,&quot;7362DF 16GW supports two powering options: AC and DC power. Optional Field-replaceable Dust filter can be selected to protect the equipment against dust. Optional Mechanical Mounting kits options allow to equip the 7362 DF 16GW either in an ETSI rack or in a 19 inch rack.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;FASTERMIND&apos;,&quot;Please select the Fastermind features&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;7363ISAMMX6&apos;,&quot;7363 ISAM MX-6 supports following technologies: System Level Vectoring (SLV) VDSL2 17a, Vplus/ VDSL2 35b, P2P and Voice. Please select the technology and number of ports needed. The number of LT boards is limited to 6 (5 in case of AC powering).&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &quot;7705SAR8&quot;,&quot;Please select the power environment you are installing the system in, if you require conformal coating, AC power options and CSM redundancy.&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;DATREF&apos;,&quot;Please select the Data Refinery features&quot;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &quot;MPW&quot;,&apos;Please provide the number of additional dispatch consoles (on top of the initial 5 licenses included with GC Server license).&apos;,IF(Apttus_Config2__LineItemId__r.Apttus_Config2__ProductId__r.ProductCode == &apos;7750SRe&apos;,&quot;Please selct the IOM-e type required and the MDA-es to meet your connectivity needs. &quot;,&quot;The 4-wavelength CWDM dual-fiber SAR-O is used to drop and add four specific wavelengths from the network; other wavelengths are allowed to pass through. The SAR-O can also add other wavelengths and allow a 1310 nm signal to pass through in the case of a CWDM OADM linear 1310 nm application.The 1471-1531 model is used to drop and add the following four wavelengths: • 1471/1491/1511/1531 nm The 1551-1611 model is used to drop and add the following four wavelengths: • 1551/1571/1591/1611 nm The 1271-1331 model is used to drop and add the following four wavelengths: • 1271/1291/1311/1331 nm The 1351-1451 model is used to drop and add the following four wavelengths: • 1351/1371/1431/1451 nm&quot;)))))))))))</formula>
    <formulaTreatBlanksAs>BlankAsZero</formulaTreatBlanksAs>
    <label>Guidance</label>
    <required>false</required>
    <trackTrending>false</trackTrending>
    <type>Text</type>
    <unique>false</unique>
</CustomField>
