<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokCorp.Partner.All.D.E.E.17250.PAC Rome We missed you e-mail sendout.Thank y</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>2017 Partner Advisory Council, Rome, Italy</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
PAC 2017
Thank you for attending the Nokia Partner Advisory Council in Rome

Thank you for taking the time to meet with us in Rome, Italy and sharing your valuable insights on the market and Nokia’s Global Partner Program and strategy. 

Our executive team firmly believes that the success of any partnership is based on trust and dialog. It was important for us to share with you the commitment and investment Nokia is making in the Channel Partner model. That includes a new Configure/Price/Quote tool, new IP, WiFi, and Optical Networks products, and focus on segments such as Smart Cities. Obviously, the conversations we had are only the beginning. All of us at Nokia look forward to working with you and the rest of our partner community to continue to improve our overall partnership and to put into action the suggestions you offered. 

The presentations from the 2017 Partner Advisory Council are now available for download &lt;[[https://resources.ext.nokia.com/asset/201617]]&gt;. The password to access the file is: PAC2017.

 If you did not have the chance in Rome at the end of the meeting to complete the short survey &lt;[[https://www.research.net/r/EMEAPAC2]]&gt;, I hope you will take the time to complete it now and provide us your valuable insights. This survey will help us improve the Council summits so that we can continue to have meaningful and fruitful discussions as we work together to improve our joint business initiatives and the partner program. 

Thank you again and we look forward to continuing our dialog and following up with you on a quaterly basis. 

Sincerely, 
Ismael Hassa
Head of Partner Management, MEA
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
