<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-TEPS-Utilities Moderniz.-Email-EngInviteWebinar2-T0028Q.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Webinar invite: Modernising communications without compromising critical legacy systems</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
26 September, 2018
14:00 London / 15:00 Paris / 21:00 Singapore / 9:00 New York
Modernising communications without compromising critical legacy systems
Deploying modern communications networks is a key part of achieving an efficient, reliable grid. But migrating traffic of legacy systems onto the new networks is not a simple process. It is necessary that the migration is graceful, and does not compromise system performance nor cause operations disruption. 

In Modernising communications without compromising critical legacy systems, we will explore how Oncor Electric Delivery, which operates one of the largest transmission and distribution systems in the US, executed a smooth migration of their legacy system traffic from their time-division multiplexing solution network. We will take a closer look at their experiences and how their partnership with Nokia enabled a more responsive and adaptive network. 

 Tune in on Wednesday 26th September to learn:


	- Key architectural considerations Oncor Electric Delivery identified for migrating critical legacy systems to IP/MPLS and their learning from this migration.
	- How migrating to an IP/MPLS network prepares a utility for future capabilities such as Industrial Internet of Things and IEC 61850 standard.
	- How both operational efficiency and customer service can be improved thanks to the modernisation efforts.
Speakers
Hansen Chan 
Marketing Manager, Nokia
John Alberti 
Senior Network Architect, Oncor
Keen to find out more? Register your place &lt;[[https://www.engerati.com/transmission-and-distribution/webinars/communications-networks-technologies/modernising?utm_source=Nokia%20Article%20Guest1&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_campaign=Nokia%20Migration%20Emails]]&gt; to make sure you don&apos;t miss out.
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
