<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Partners-Newsletters-Email-Q4 Newsletter-T003BS.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Nokia Partner Flash - your quarterly news</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
DECEMBER 2018
Partner Flash - your quarterly news
In this issue:
Program News &lt;[[#programnews]]&gt; | Marketing &lt;[[#marketing]]&gt; | Success Stories &lt;[[#success]]&gt; | Featured Solutions and Technology &lt;[[#product]]&gt; | Partner Spotlight &lt;[[#spotlight]]&gt; | Videos &lt;[[#videos]]&gt; | Tools and Training &lt;[[#tools]]&gt; | Market Trends &lt;[[#training]]&gt; | Events &lt;[[#events]]&gt; | Upcoming Events &lt;[[#upcoming]]&gt;
Program News
Nokia&apos;s Large Enterprise and Webscale lead speaks on Digital Transformation
In business, there are moments that push us beyond traditional boundaries in order to deliver a greater outcome. That’s where many of our customers are right now, and what we need to do to help them address the challenges.” – Mike Calabrese, Head of Large Enterprise and Webscale. In this interview, you will learn how Nokia and partners can seize new digital transformation opportunities … together!
Read interview →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0692M00000IE9d2QAD?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Transportation, Energy, Public Sector interview →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000DmIGyAAN?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Enterprise marketing strategy interview →  &lt;[[http://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0684100000D5pgtAAB?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Partner 1st strategy interview →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=06941000007DqgsAAC?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Nokia forms dedicated Enterprise Business Group
Nokia has expanded its effort to address high-growth, high-margin opportunities with a set of enterprise and industry customers needing telco-grade networks. Toward this end we have established a new Enterprise Business Group that consolidates a range of existing, fast-growing activities into one focused organization under the leadership of Kathrin Buvac, currently Nokia&apos;s Chief Strategy Officer.
Read press release →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/news/releases/2018/10/25/nokia-announces-plans-to-accelerate-strategy-execution-sharpen-customer-focus-and-maintain-long-term-cost-leadership?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Nokia’s Gifts &amp; Hospitality Guidelines – A Year-End Refresher
As we approach the festive season, we would like to remind you on Nokia’s guidelines on hospitality. Nokia believes in doing business fairly. Gifts, hospitality or other benefits should never be offered, promised or given to a government official, third party or customer with the intent to obtain any business advantage or improperly influence any action or decision. Similarly, we discourage hospitality and gifts to be given to Nokia employees that may influence or be perceived to influence decision making. For any questions, please contact your Nokia business representative and/or ethics@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:ethics@nokia.com]]&gt;.
Nokia Commercial Third Party Code of Conduct →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000CDhfLAAT?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;Nokia Ethics Hotline →  &lt;[[http://www.nokia.ethicspoint.com?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Marketing
NEW! Calling all visionary people
By 2020, analysts are forecasting there will be 8 billion people, 20 billion connected devices and 1 trillion apps connecting everyone and everything. The race to digitize has begun. To help your customers drive extreme automation to deliver increased efficiency, richer customer experiences and boost business performance in this new age of industry, explore how we can help shape the future together with innovative enterprise networking solutions from Nokia. Ready to Go Allwhere? We’re ready to go with you!
Webpage →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/networks/go-allwhere?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;White Paper →  &lt;[[https://onestore.nokia.com/asset/205709?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;Case Study → &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?index=2&amp;list=PLgKNvl454Bxc4KGmWJc_eeBb4VD0TJ41R&amp;v=US2q0mXQ8Oo?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Let us reward your sales efforts
Nokia is trialing a new incentive program. If you have not already done so, it’s not too late to get accredited and certified on Nokia Optical LAN (formerly POL) technology. Help us make this program a success by participating so we can continue offering exciting sales incentive programs in the future. It’s easy to participate. Simply register and close approved Nokia Optical LAN (formerly POL) deals to begin earning prizes.
Executive summary presentation → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Nokia-Optical-LAN-Incentive-Program]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Success Stories
Nokia Bell Labs wins its 9th Nobel Prize
Nokia has a heritage of some of the brightest minds. Arthur Ashkin, a former Bell Laboratories researcher, was awarded the 2018 Nobel Prize in Physics “for the optical tweezers and their application to biological systems” on October 2, 2018. The Royal Swedish Academy of Sciences administers the Nobel Prize for Physics and said they were awarding this year’s winners “for groundbreaking inventions in the field of laser physics.”
Read blog →  &lt;[[https://www.bell-labs.com/var/articles/2018-nobel-prize-physics?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;Webpage →  &lt;[[https://www.bell-labs.com/var/articles/arthur-ashkin-nobel-prize?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;Nokia awards → &lt;[[https://www.bell-labs.com/about/recognition?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Featured Solutions and Technology
Unveiling Future X: the blueprint for network evolution
Nokia recently introduced its &apos;Future X for industries&apos; strategy and architecture, developed by Bell Labs, to drive dramatic productivity improvements across a wide range of industry sectors. As technologies such as industrial Internet of Things (IIoT); edge cloud supporting augmented intelligence and advanced security analytics; and end-to-end 5G capable networks become a reality, they will radically speed up the digital transformation of industries such as manufacturing, logistics, transportation and energy, as well as governments and cities. Nokia&apos;s holistic approach promises to help drive a new era of productivity and human-machine interaction that will unlock trillions of dollars of economic value in the next decade.
Read press release →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/news/releases/2018/11/07/nokia-unveils-future-x-for-industries-strategy-and-architecture-to-catalyze-productivity-and-economic-growth-in-the-industry-40-era?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Nokia WaveLite helps enterprises with digital transformation
Healthcare providers, banks, and sports venues are a few examples of how Nokia WaveLite is helping enterprises better serve their customers through private optical networks. WaveLite helps these organizations gain greater control over their networks and optimize cost through a network dedicated to their unique needs. Built with enterprise needs in mind, WaveLite complements Nokia’s optical portfolio with a 200Gbps optical transport solution capable of aggregating a wide range of services and speeds over metro and regional networks. Supported by a strong set of sales and training tools, and proven through deployments across the world, WaveLite is now ready for widescale deployment by our partners. Contact you partner sales manager for more information.
Training →  &lt;[[https://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1516223244466?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Marketing Collateral →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/WaveLite-PRM?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Partner Spotlight
Nokia strikes Infosys deal that targets enterprise digitization
Nokia and Infosys, a global leader in consulting, technology and next-generation services, have established a strategic alliance to drive digital transformation in a wide array of enterprises and industries, addressing vertical markets including transportation, energy and manufacturing, media and entertainment and education. This collaboration will couple technology, products and services from Nokia with platform solutions, engineering and operations management expertise from Infosys.
Press release → &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/news/releases/2018/11/07/nokia-and-infosys-establish-strategic-alliance-to-support-the-digital-transformation-of-major-industries-and-enterprises?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Successful distributorship model in Korea
In the competitive South Korean market, Nokia needed to find innovative ways to serve growing demand. To help capture growth opportunities in this market and to simplify its dealings with enterprise partners, Nokia shifted its business approach to a sole distributorship model. In January 2017, Nokia appointed DKUNC, a well-established ICT service provider, as its single major distributor in South Korea. DKUNC prides itself on its ICT innovation and providing its customers with value in new services and competitiveness through creative ideas and advanced IT technologies. The model has been a win-win for all with resellers enjoying dedicated support, DKUNC winning new growth opportunities with expectations to triple growth in its business with Nokia in the next few years, and Nokia having a more streamlined and efficient way of getting products to a wider range of customers.
To learn more about this success story and how to implement it in your business, contact your Nokia Partner Sales manager today!
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Videos
Nokia edge cloud
Cloud computing is transforming our landscape, offering flexibility and lower total costs, plus high service availability. Yet current cloud-based networks rely on centralized architecture. The drawback is that this architecture cannot cost-effectively support the ultra-low latency and extreme throughput demanded by the Internet of Things and 5G. But now we have a solution for your enterprise customers and their data centers. Explore how Edge cloud takes compute capacity to where the traffic is.
Watch video → &lt;[[https://youtu.be/nlb7K5Tg3rY?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Go Allwhere!
The race to digitize has begun. By 2020, analysts are forecasting there will be 8 billion people, 20 billion connected devices and 1 trillion apps connecting everyone and everything. To help your customers drive extreme automation to deliver increased efficiency, richer customer experiences and boost business performance in this new age of industry, explore how we can help shape the future together with innovative enterprise networking solutions from Nokia. Ready to Go Allwhere? We’re ready to go with you!
Watch video → &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SSYuqaB709Q?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Tools and Training
NEW! Tools to help you close out 2018
As year-end approaches, things get busy. Whether you are trying to close deals, use Co-op funds, or get certified, the Nokia Partner Portal provides the tools you need to get things done. And best of all, built-in self-service capabilities allow you to manage critical year-end activities according to your timeline. Simply access the Nokia Partner Portal and all its tools to get your job done.
Partner Portal → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Featured new training this month


	- Library Training for Library Administrators &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0692M00000IDqvbQAD]]&gt; New
	- Partner Changes to Quote section of CPQ &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000GTcRlAAL]]&gt; New
	- External Task Management &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000Dm5aqAAB]]&gt; New
	- Co-op for Partners &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000Dm5bKAAR]]&gt; New


Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Market Trends
SD-WAN technology sales forecasted to reach $4.5 bln in 2022
With over 400 enterprise customers, Nuage Networks Virtualized Network Services platform is increasingly the choice of global carriers and enterprises looking to automate, secure and optimize their IT processes as well as their WAN, datacenter and public cloud networks. Get a piece of the pie by offering the industry’s only automated and secure services platform for the delivery of enterprise IT services across any network and cloud with SD-WAN 2.0 from Nuage Networks.
Press release →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/releases/2018/09/19/nuage-networks-unveils-sd-wan-20-the-industrys-only-automated-and-secure-services-platform-for-the-delivery-of-enterprise-it-services-across-any-network-and-cloud?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Events
Partner Roadshows
Partner roadshows were recently held in Singapore and Malaysia. Both events provided yet another great opportunity to talk about the various Enterprise segments of Nokia and to have in-depth discussions with segment experts about solutions and use cases..
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Gartner Symposium and Tech Summit in Goa
Nokia sponsored the Gartner enterprise Symposium, one of the largest events for enterprises in India with participation from around 1000+ CIOs/IT heads from the industry across all segments – BFSI, data centers, retail, automotive, utilities, manufacturing, and healthcare. We unveiled the Nokia for Industries campaign branding at the event and also hosted an exclusive CIO lunch which was very well attended by our Enterprise customers.
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
SReXperts in Singapore
Nokia held the 7th annual SReXperts APAC Convention from 16-18 October 2018 in Singapore. This world-class education and training event has been designed to leverage customer’s investment in Nokia’s IP portfolios.
Converge
At this event, Nokia hosted partners who had the opportunity to learn and hear more about Nokia Future X from Marcus Weldon, CTO and President Nokia Bell Labs. Nokia 5G Future X is the first end-to-end 5G portfolio of solutions, software and services to fulfil all these needs, providing Communications Service Providers (CSPs) with the opportunity to take early advantage of the promise of 5G.
Nokia webpage → &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/5g/5g-future-x?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;

HPE Discover
By 2020, approximately 75% of the global population will be connected by mobile. But these connections don’t happen without the underlying network infrastructure. We’re seeing and feeling the impacts of digital transformation, IoT and the cloud as it affects all aspects of our daily lives in some very profound ways. Read our blog to learn how the story unfolds.
Read blog → &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/blog/making-global-iot-connectivity-reality?did=d0000000016v&amp;utm_campaign=newsletters&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Upcoming Events
Mobile World Congress 2019 &lt;[[https://www.mwcbarcelona.com/]]&gt;


25 – 28 February 2019
Barcelona, Spain



Optical Fiber Communication Conference &amp; Exhibition (OFC) &lt;[[https://www.ofcconference.org/en-us/home/]]&gt;

03 – 07 March 2019
San Diego, CA



World ATM Congress &lt;[[https://www.worldatmcongress.org/home]]&gt;


12 – 14 March 2019
Madrid, Spain




MPLS+SDN+NFV World 2019 &lt;[[https://www.uppersideconferences.com/mpls-sdn-nfv/]]&gt;

09 – 12 April 2019
Paris, France


Intertraffic &lt;[[https://www.intertraffic.com/]]&gt;


10 – 12 April 2019
Istanbul
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
