<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Util Crit Comms-Util Architecture-Email-Informa Invite-T0029L.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Webinar: Optimizing Energy Asset Lifecycles with Predictive Analytics</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Optimizing energy asset lifecycles with predictive analytics
Explore the world of advanced analytics
3 October, 2018 at 2:00pm ET / 11:00am PT
The utility sector faces ever-shrinking revenue streams and an on-going battle to manage CapEx and OpEx efficiency; predictive maintenance, risk assessment and capital planning have never been more important. Using advanced analytics to develop a risk-based approach to asset maintenance and capital planning is critical to companies managing legacy assets while simultaneously supporting the transition to renewable and distributed energy.

Join our panelists, with special guest and industry expert, John Di Stasio, President of the Large Public Power Council (LPPC) for this webinar &lt;[[https://utilityanalytics.com/webinar/optimizing-energy-asset-lifecycles-with-predictive-analytics?partnerref=Nokiapromo]]&gt; to learn how using advanced analytics helps companies:


	- Lower operating costs.
	- Reduce risk and outages.
	- Improve regulatory compliance and reliability.
	- Take control of capital expenditure planning, unbundled regulatory models, dynamic pricing and digital customer service.


And hear how Nokia Asset Lifecycle Optimization has made a difference in real-world operations.
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
