<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokCorp.Partner.All.D.N.E.19196.Partners&apos; Lightspeed e-mail 2 delivery.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Jump start your grid modernization</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Jump start your grid modernization with broadband communications
Dear {{lead.Full Name:default=Sir/Madame}}, 
 
Municipal utilities and electric cooperatives face the challenges of making their distribution grids smarter, more reliable, and capable of supporting renewable generation sources and storage while cutting demand peaks and thereby reducing supply costs. 

Broadband communications can be leveraged to support Smart Grid technology, along with consumer broadband internet access services to generate the revenue needed to quickly recoup the broadband investment. Opelika Power Services has done just that.

 Opelika Power Services deployed a city-wide broadband installation enabling high-quality triple-play services, for residents and businesses, and a smarter grid. This advanced communications platform was the first of its kind in Alabama. 

With Nokia’s end-to-end FTTH technologies, partnered with Lightspeed services capabilities, we can help you enable community prosperity through gigabit broadband service. Learn more by downloading the Opelika case study.
LightSpeed Technologies was recently named Nokia’s #1 Business Partner, specializing in broadband/FTTx networking solutions. Since 2001 LightSpeed has been assisting utilities and municipalities with initial systems engineering, material management, product Installation and system testing and turn-up as well as on-going maintenance support. We welcome the opportunity to demonstrate to your organization our renowned customer service and technical assistance. 

Contact us to get answers to your questions today! 

For more information please contact: 
Joe Caruso 
LightSpeed 
917 882 8455 
joecaruso@lightspeedt.com  &lt;[[mailto:joecaruso@lightspeedt.com]]&gt;
www.lightspeedt.com &lt;[[http://www.lightspeedt.com]]&gt;
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
