<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.IPRout.Energy.Utility.L.E.E.15818.EUW 2017 Eblast.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Invitation: Be our guest at EUW 2017</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Nokia has been named the leader in Low Power Wide Area (LPWA) networking for utilities by Navigant Research &lt;[[https://www.navigantresearch.com/research/navigant-research-leaderboard-power-utility-low-power-wide-area-networking-vendors]]&gt;. Nokia was chosen over 14 other equipment vendors and service providers, and is favorably positioned for the evolution of the power grid with IoT.





 European Utility Week (EUW)  3-5 October, 2017  RAI, Amsterdam, Netherlands





Learn more about the Nokia NB-IoT solution by attending our seminar 
Register for a private LTE network and cyber security seminar on Tuesday, 3 October, 17.30 – 19.00, where we will cover two topics: 


	- Private LTE networks: Find out about the private LTE network solution a utility builds and owns, initial use cases that US utilities identified for their deployments, planning activities, and a tool to quantify its financial impact.
	- Cyber security solutions for critical networks: Learn how you can effectively account for elements of logical security that meet and exceed current compliance requirements, within a multi-vendor IT and OT environment. 


Seminar will be held at the RAI, Amsterdam, Netherlands. Join your peers at a reception after this seminar which is solely for utility personnel. Please RSVP to Mari Holmstrom &lt;[[mailto:mari.holmstrom@nokia.com]]&gt; by 22 September.
 
For complete event information on EUW 2017, please visit: http://www.european-utility-week.com/  &lt;[[http://www.european-utility-week.com/]]&gt;
Learn more about Nokia’s Solutions for Utilities &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/power-utilities]]&gt;. 

Join us at European Utility Week at Nokia booth 1L22, 3-5 October in Amsterdam.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
