<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.BBAccess.Intelligent.Services.N.G.N.18224.TBC.Email 1 - Generic Federico vide</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Whatever your network needs, intelligent access has you covered</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Welcome to the era of intelligent access
How are you planning to meet your bandwidth and coverage targets while managing increasing complexity in your broadband network?
Whether you need to make your network faster, better or smarter, Nokia intelligent access &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access]]&gt; has you covered.


	- Deliver ultra-broadband to more people, more quickly with the perfect combination of FTTx &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/fttx]]&gt; technologies.
	- Maximize ultra-broadband coverage and network efficiencies with fixed-mobile convergence &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/fixed-mobile-convergence]]&gt; solutions.
	- Unleash new capacity in cable networks &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/cable]]&gt; with distributed architectures, DOCSIS 3.1 and deep fiber.
	- Eliminate the weakest link by extending gigabit services throughout the digital home &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/digital-home]]&gt; and unlocking new revenue opportunities.
	- Virtualize and automate your network &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/virtualization-automation]]&gt; to master complexity, reduce costs and increase operational agility.
	- Employ our expertise, analytics and automated services &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access/services]]&gt; for a right-first-time migration or network upgrade.


Hear from Federico Guillén &lt;[[http://networks.nokia.com/intelligent-access#bbwf]]&gt;, president of Nokia&apos;s Fixed Networks Business Group, talking about what Nokia intelligent access can do for you.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
