<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Partners TO-Operational Comms-Email-Partner Portal-T002FX.Subject Line Test</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Tools to help close year-end business</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Dear Partner,

 As year-end approaches, things get busy. Very busy. Whether you are trying to close deals, use Co-op funds, or get certified, the Nokia Partner Portal provides the tools you need to get things done. And best of all, built-in self-service capabilities allow you to manage critical year-end activities according to your timeline. Consider the following …
Situation: Jack is a busy sales rep who is running out of time. He struggles to wrap up year-end activities quickly but only has 2 months remaining to reach his 2018 sales objective. Good news is, he has a customer interested in a Passive Optical LAN networking solution. But how can he quickly close a deal to meet his annual sales objective?
Solution: The Nokia Partner Portal &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/%3e]]&gt; provides Jack and his Sales Engineer, Peter, with self-service capabilities to configure, price and quote Nokia products and solutions. He no longer needs to wait for support from Nokia to respond to his customer. But wait … Peter does not have access to the CPQ (Configure/Price/Quote) tool. What should he do?
Next steps: Peter contacts his Partner Relationship Manager or his Nokia Sales Manager who can request access to the CPQ tool in “Additional Resources” area of the Portal. Please note: Granting access may take 24 – 48 hours. Either way, Jack and Peter are on the path to getting a quote completed quickly for the solution and maintenance to close the deal this year.
Why is this important? Jack successfully closes the deal without delays. He meets his sales objective. If you are looking for a way to quickly complete sales activities before the year comes crashing to a close, look no further. Simply access the Nokia Partner Portal and all its tools to get your job done. Please contact your Partner Sales Manager for assistance. Training for the Nokia Partner Portal including the tools can be found at: https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/PRM-Training-PRM &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/PRM-Training-PRM]]&gt;


The Nokia Global Partner Program
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
