<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-TEPS-Transportation-Email-ATM Thx email-T001YV.Email 01</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>It was great to see you at ATM World Congress</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Prioritizing safety and security in every connection
Thank you for joining us at ATM World Congress; it was a pleasure to welcome you at our booth. We hope that you found it was worthwhile to engage with us, meet industry colleagues and find out how Nokia can be your trusted partner to make air traffic control safer.
Throughout the event there were a lot of discussions about our advanced critical communication solutions for air traffic management. We kindly thank you for the conversations and for your feedback.


A couple of resources that you might find useful are identified below:



	- Mission-critical communications networks for air traffic management &lt;[[https://resources.nokia.com/asset/200376]]&gt;. Air Navigation Service Providers (ANSPs) must control and guarantee the safe and efficient movement of aircraft in the sky and at airports while addressing a huge number of new challenges (traffic increase, drones, cyber security, migration, interoperability) This white paper describes the Nokia networking solutions available to ANSPs who need to meet today’s demands while preparing for the future.
	- Video on Nokia solution for Airports &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ruo-EyLk5YQ]]&gt;. This video showcases how to connect flights by supporting passenger, cargo, airport and air traffic, and control operations on a single intelligent airport communications network to enhance airport performance, customer experience, safety and efficiency.


If you wish to stay updated with the latest Nokia Aviation solutions, please visit our website &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/aviation]]&gt; and for any questions, do not hesitate to contact us &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/how-to-buy]]&gt;.


Yours sincerely,
The Nokia team
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
