<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-NFI:TEPS_TXLE-Partners noncampaign-Email-Q1 Newsletter-T003OL.Newsletter</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Nokia Partner Flash - your quarterly news</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
MARCH 2019
Partner Flash - your quarterly news
In this issue:
Marketing &lt;[[#marketing]]&gt; | Testimonials &lt;[[#Testimonials]]&gt; | Press Releases &lt;[[#press]]&gt; | Success Stories &lt;[[#success]]&gt; | Branding &lt;[[#branding]]&gt; | Tools and Training &lt;[[#tools]]&gt; | Events &lt;[[#events]]&gt; | Upcoming Events &lt;[[#upcoming]]&gt;
Marketing
What is Allwhere?
Whether your customer is in Transportation, Utilities or Public Safety, they have networking needs in common. In this new age of industry, your customers need IoT for all the sensors &amp; devices and connected machines, with high-performance networking, a multi-cloud infrastructure, digital platforms, and security at every level. Each of these network elements provide the needed infrastructure to run all the business applications specific to your customer’s industry.
With Nokia, our Future X for industries architecture can be tuned for every industry segment, and the business applications specific to your customer’s environment. All the rest – high performance networking, multi-cloud infrastructure, digital platforms, and security – stays exactly the same and applies to every industry, in a very consistent way.
Explore how we can help shape the future together with innovative enterprise networking solutions from Nokia. Ready to Go Allwhere? We’re ready to go with you!
 Watch Allwhere video → &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SSYuqaB709Q]]&gt;
Read “The Automation of Everything” blog →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/blog/industry-40-revolution-here-automation-everything/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Read “5 things you can do better with Industry 4.0” blog → &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/blog/5-things-you-can-do-better-industry-40/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Rewarding your sales efforts
Nokia has now launched an incentive program for qualified partners. Join your industry peers who have already begun earning prizes by closing approved Nokia Optical LAN (formerly POL) deals. If you are certified and your company is accredited on Nokia Optical LAN technology, or if you are actively selling or have sold our POL solution in the past, you may be eligible to participate. Simply contact your Nokia Partner Sales Manager to see if you qualify.
Exec presentation → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Nokia-Optical-LAN-Incentive-Program]]&gt; POL Training → &lt;[[https://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/item/n.1489518527001]]&gt; Optical LAN on Partner Portal → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Passive-Optical-LAN-PRM]]&gt;
What is a micro moment?
The I want-to-know moments, I want-to-go moments, I want-to-do moments, and I want-to-buy moments. We call these &quot;micro-moments,&quot; and they&apos;re game changers for both consumers and brands.
Micro-moments occur when people reflexively turn to a device to act on a need to learn something, do something, discover something, watch something, or buy something. They are intent-rich moments when decisions are made and preferences shaped. In these moments, consumers&apos; expectations are higher than ever. The powerful computers we carry in our pockets have trained us to expect brands to immediately deliver exactly what we are looking for when we are looking (Sridhar Ramaswamy, Senior Vice President of Ads &amp; Commerce at Google). We want things right, and we want things right away as illustrated in a true micro moment of a Nokia employee.
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
“Technology to connect the world” as it relates to ‘my world’
As a Type 1 diabetic, I rely heavily on technology every minute of each day. My insulin pump and continuous glucose monitor connect over WiFi to the cloud, sending my glucose readings to my cell phone. This allows me to make informed decisions on the go and in real-time about how best to manage my disease, in addition to sharing my data with family members and doctors. The technology is indeed impressive. But none of this would at all be possible without a network that seamlessly connects me, my devices, and my healthcare professionals, allowing me to live a full and healthy life. – Terri Edmunds, Partner Marketing &amp; Communications at Nokia
Do you have a micro moment you’d like to share about what technology means to you? We’d like to hear your stories.
Contact Nokia → &lt;[[mailto:terri.edmunds@nokia.com?subject=I%20have%20a%20micro%20moment%20I]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Testimonials
Nokia, LightSpeed and WG+E brings ultra-fast broadband to rural America
Many rural towns in Massachusetts have no access to broadband, wireless internet or cable TV. With the goal of providing a world-class solution to this challenge, utility company Westfield Gas &amp; Electric selected LightSpeed Technologies and Nokia to roll out ultra-fast broadband to 20 underserved rural communities. Learn more by watching our video of the birth of connectivity in the Town of Otis through this successful partnering.
Watch video → &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=J_ngNgsUHUs]]&gt;
Do you have a success story to share? To submit your idea for a future feature story, please contact us &lt;[[mailto:nokia_global_partner_communications@nokia.com?subject=Partner%20success%20story%20for%20Terri%20Edmunds]]&gt;.
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Empowering a new innovation society
BE ALL chose Nokia’s Optical LAN to power their shared workspace facility comprised of 2,870 workstations on 9 floors. The Nokia solution delivers a high capacity, future-proof and always on network, and provides all the connectivity needed for tenants at ALON Tower in Tel Aviv, Israel.
Watch video → &lt;[[https://youtu.be/2BVEULjuYgo]]&gt;
650 Group
“As a leading IP routing, optical and SDN vendor and top supplier to hyperscalers, Nokia is well positioned to provide equipment and software to help webscale companies rapidly grow their cloud network operations to enable exceptional customer experiences.” Chris DePuy, Technology Analyst and Founder, 650 Group
IP Routing → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/IP-Routing-PRM]]&gt; Optical → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/IP-Transport-PRM]]&gt; SDN → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/SDN-Nuage-Networks-PRM]]&gt;
DE-CIX 
“DE-CIX values Nokia’s multi-terabit FP4 silicon innovation that drives best-in-class capacity, density and efficiency in 7950 XRS routing platforms. DE-CIX continues its partnership with Nokia to deploy the world’s biggest and most capable routers at the heart of our exchange”. Daniel Melzer, CTO at DE-CIX
7950 XRS on Partner Portal→ &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/7950-Extensible-Routing-System-PRM]]&gt;
ACG
“Webscale operators are building bigger networks to connect resources across the globe and bring data centers closer to users for the highest performance. Nokia has managed to combine the raw horsepower required to run historic amounts of traffic between data centers with intelligent, secure and adaptable capabilities necessary for a cloud connected environment.” Ray Mota, CEO &amp; Principal Analyst, ACG
Article → &lt;[[https://pf.content.nokia.com/networking-at-webscale/what-the-market-says?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Press Releases
Nokia joins forces with Facebook’s Express Wi-Fi Technology Partner program to build better Wi-Fi networks
Internet service providers and mobile network operators participating in Facebook&apos;s Express Wi-Fi program can deploy the cloud-based Nokia AirScale Wi-Fi platform to their network hardware, helping to bring more people online globally.
Read press release →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/news/releases/2019/02/25/nokia-joins-facebooks-express-wi-fi-technology-partner-program-to-build-better-wi-fi-networks/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Nokia AirScale Wi-Fi platform →  &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/products/smart-wi-fi?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; AirScale Wi-Fi on Partner Portal →  &lt;https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Wi-Fi-PRM&gt;
A first-of-its-kind initiative in India
Bharti Airtel to use Nokia’s Nuage Networks solution for data center automation.
Read press release → &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/news/releases/2019/02/27/mwc19-airtel-to-use-nokias-nuage-networks-solution-for-data-center-automation-in-a-first-of-its-kind-initiative-in-india/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Getting started with Nokia
One of the key benefits of joining the Nokia Partner Program is market recognition you and your company gain in the association with a well-known, established global company and brand, recognized for its leadership in technology and innovation. Nokia Partners are a vital part of our sales force and for the enterprise and public sector markets. That means we want to help you take advantage of that market positioning by supporting your media relations efforts, both when you join the program and to promote successes. Below are guidelines to get you started.
Partner Press &amp; Media guidelines →  &lt;https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=06941000001uTBgAAM&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Success Stories
Nokia named one of the World’s Most Ethical Companies for 2019. This honor is bestowed by the Ethisphere Institute, a leading organization for corporate ethics, on companies that demonstrate a commitment to integrity, a robust compliance program, and a strong corporate culture. This recognition brings value to our business and is meaningful to customers around the world. Please contact us to discuss how we can continue to partner and enhance our strong commitment to a culture of integrity.
&quot;World&apos;s Most Ethical Companies&quot; and &quot;Ethisphere&quot; names and marks are registered trademarks of Ethisphere LLC.
Read story →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/nokia-once-again-named-one-of-the-worlds-most-ethical-companies/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; Contact us → &lt;[[mailto:ethics@nokia.com]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Nokia leadership in IP Routing 
Nokia maintains #1 market share position against competitors in IP Routing market in EMEA for second year in a row (Dell’Oro, 2019).
Watch IP Routing demo room video →  &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1dZ1GJCXodM]]&gt;  IP Routing on Partner Portal → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/IP-Routing-PRM]]&gt;
Subsea solution in the Australian outback
Nokia worked side-by-side with a partner to build a new private optical network for an electricity distributor in Australia. The network will be used for advanced remote automation of solar and wind farms in the Australian outback and for the customer’s data center connectivity needs.
1830 PSS Nokia webpage →  &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/products/1830-photonic-service-switch?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt; 1830 PSS on Partner Portal →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/1830-Photonic-Service-Switch-PRM]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Branding
Brand reputation matters  
Brand Finance has just published its 2019 Global 500 Brand Report of the world’s most valuable brands. The results show the Nokia brand value has increased +17%. As partners position solutions with customers, feel confident that the Nokia brand continues to make great strides among some of the world’s best companies. 
Brand report → &lt;[[http://brandfinance.com/knowledge-centre/reports/brand-finance-global-500-2019/&quot;]]&gt; 
 Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Deconstructing the Nokia brand and tagline 
We are optimistic about the future. We believe in the potential of digital technologies to ignite a new era or opportunity – for business, for industry and for people everywhere. That’s why, “We create the technology to connect the world”. To create new possibilities for human togetherness, experience and productivity. To make technology work for people. We push the boundaries of what’s possible to unlock opportunities from an intensely connected world – always from a foundation of integrity, quality and security.
”We create the technology” Banner → &lt;http://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000CC4O9AAL&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Tools and Training
The Partner Learning Store goes mobile 
Speed. Innovation. Agility. Winning starts with the right training … in the right format.
Success today requires a workforce with the skills to compete effectively. The Nokia Partner Learning Store is our education learning platform for training programs designed to ensure partners have the product knowledge needed to be highly effective.
But in today’s digital world, we need learning at our fingertips … on any device at any time. That’s why we are happy to report that The Learning Store has gone mobile, allowing you to learn on the go from any mobile device - iPhone, iPad, Windows phone and Android.
Partner Learning Store → &lt;[[https://learningstore.nokia.com/partner]]&gt; Training catalogs and schedules → &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Training-PRM]]&gt;
Get the most out of your Co-op funds 
Our Co-op Program is designed to support partners in effectively marketing Nokia products and solutions. Use your Co-op reimbursement funds to tailor your advertising, marketing, and business development efforts to promote and sell Nokia products and solutions. Explore our new Co-op training for additional program details.
Co-op training &lt;https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0694100000Dm5bKAAR&gt; - New
Nokia AirScale Wi-Fi pricing now in the CPQ tool 
The Nokia Configure Price Quote tool which has been designed to enable presales capabilities to easily generate quotes for your projects continues to evolve. Among other evolutions, we just introduced AirScale Wi-Fi into the tool. From the Partner Portal get trained on the tool in “Topic Catalog” → “Partner Portal Training”. If you need access to the CPQ tool, you will find instructions here &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0692M00000J9EDnQAN]]&gt;.
AirScale CPQ Training →  &lt;https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0692M00000J9EECQA3&gt;
 AirScale Wi-Fi Ordering Guide (ppt) →  &lt;https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/documentpage?Id=0692M00000JUjaAQAT&gt;
 AirScale Wi-Fi on Partner Portal →  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Wi-Fi-PRM]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Events
Mobile World Congress 
See how Nokia created the technology to connect the world at MWC this year.
Watch “A tour of the Nokia stand at MWC” video →  &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gJGASYfe8-Y]]&gt;
 Watch “Connected Industries” video →  &lt;[[https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xtkXu3wOT0E]]&gt;
 Nokia at MWC →  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/networks/mwc/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Upcoming Events
APAC Rail &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/events/calendar/apac-rail-2019/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;

19 – 20 March
Hong Kong


Hannover Messe  &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/events/calendar/hannover-messe/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;

01 – 05 April
Hannover, Germany


MPLS+SDN+NFV World 2019 &lt;[[https://www.uppersideconferences.com/mpls-sdn-nfv/]]&gt;
09 – 12 April
Paris, France




Digital Mines Pan Pacific &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/about-us/events/calendar/digital-mines/?did=d000000001cd&amp;utm_campaign=partners_noncampaign&amp;utm_source=email-list-partner-distribution-march-2019&amp;utm_medium=email]]&gt;
10 – 12 April
Perth, Australia


Intertraffic &lt;[[https://www.intertraffic.com/amsterdam]]&gt;

21 – 24 April
RAI, Amsterdam



Coming Soon!

 Global Partner Roadshows
Back to top &gt; &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
