<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-GEPS TO-Partner-Email-PRM Rel 3.1-T001YP.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Nokia provides further enhancements to the Nokia Partner Portal</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Nokia Global Partner Program
Dear Partners, 

On February 26 we have released further enhancements to the Nokia Partner Portal &lt;[[https://my-home.alcatel-lucent.com/portal/web/partnerportal/]]&gt;. There are no changes to the roles that partner users play in the system. There are however a few important process and tool related updates to be aware of.


 



BUSINESS AREA

COMMENT







DOCUMENT MANAGEMENT 

Nokia will be replacing your “Personal Spaces” with new Salesforce-based Libraries. Libraries make it easier to share and collaborate on files, share content you like with colleagues, and quickly find what you&apos;re looking for from anywhere, on any device. 
When you log into your company’s library, you will find the folders (and all content) that were within each of your Personal spaces, too.




BUSINESS PLANNING

We’ve listened to your feedback and we’ve made some important updates to our online Business Plan template. We’ve enriched the Marketing Plan template to allow for more detailed planning. As well, the exportable business plan reports provide more granularity, down to the quarter.
An updated pre-recorded Business Plan training is available on the Portal &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/topic/0TO4100000182xYGAQ/prm-portal-training]]&gt;.




DEAL REGISTRATION

List of Action items for Deal Reg and Opportunity Management functionality are directly visible on the Home Page for easy identification of user’s open actions
Updates to Deal Registration List views and templates




LEAD MANAGEMENT

We’ve added deal prioritization. Together with your Nokia Partner Sales Manager, work the best deals first!
You have direct access to the updated training material on the Partner Portal &lt;[[https://my-home.alcatel-lucent.com/portal/web/partnerportal/]]&gt;. 


Please note:
You should have received a webinar invite related to the updated functionality. 

Next to these extended capabilities to the Partner Portal, Nokia will be making a gradual deployment to partners to benefit from an integrated Configure-Price-Quote (CPQ) engine, according to the partner’s accreditation status for the supported products. 

With CPQ, certified users will be able to run guided configuration and selling capabilities, and perform configuration validation directly from the Portal. You will also be able to generate quotes, with your pricing applied automatically. The CPQ engine triggers approval and status workflows for seamless collaboration with your Nokia Partner Sales Manager at Nokia. Approved and validated quotes can be exported for end-customer submission.
 



 
Configure-Price-Quote



	- From the Opportunity (prerequisite!), partner will be able to call the CPQ engine for guided or manual configuration, or even upload a pre-existing bill of material, and perform configuration validation.
	- Automatic Quote pricing will happen against the Partner Price List according to Partner’s accreditation level.
	- Cart submission will trigger approval workflow with Nokia. 
Once validated, Quote can be exported and submitted to end-customer.
Today, CPQ supports a limited number of Nokia’s IP, Optical and Fixed Network products. Going forward, we will expand the number of products supported and your quoting capability. 

In the weeks to come, we will invite the identified CPQ users for your respective accounts to an instructor-led in-depth training on how to use these new capabilities and gradually embark on this exciting journey together.
Who to contact for more information? 
If you would like more information about the new functionality, please contact your Partner Sales Manager at Nokia or one of below contacts.
ROLE

NAME
EMAIL








REGIONAL LEADS





NAM: Deb Hoerner or Esperanza Gomez




LAT: Deb Hoerner




APJ/India: Michael Uy




EU or MEA: Pat Goby or Edmond Osstyn










Deb.hoerner@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Deb.hoerner@nokia.com]]&gt; or Esperanza.gomez@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto: Esperanza.gomez@nokia.com]]&gt;





Deb.hoerner@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Deb.hoerner@nokia.com]]&gt;





Michael.uy@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Michael.uy@nokia.com]]&gt;





Pat.Goby@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Pat.Goby@nokia.com]]&gt; or Edmond.Osstyn@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Edmond.Osstyn@nokia.com]]&gt;









ENABLEMENT MANAGERS

Beatriz Rios-McKee
Eshani Johri
Julie Buckley


Beatriz.Rios-McKee@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Beatriz.Rios-McKee@nokia.com]]&gt;
Eshani.Johri@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Eshani.Johri@nokia.com]]&gt;
Julie.Buckley@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:Julie.Buckley@nokia.com]]&gt;




PARTNER BUSINESS CPQ EXPERTS

Chris Staszak
Richard Lipnick
Guillermo Jimenez


chris.staszak@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:chris.staszak@nokia.com]]&gt;
richard.lipnick@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:richard.lipnick@nokia.com]]&gt;
guillermo.jimenez@nokia.com  &lt;[[mailto:guillermo.jimenez@nokia.com]]&gt;
The Nokia Global Partner Program
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
