<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17-GEPS-XLE-Email-SBC for E Nurture-T001ZO.Email 1 Awareness</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>How to protect enterprise communications in the age of cyberattacks</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Webinar 

Digital transformation without compromising security
The rise of mobility and BYOD, along with enterprise digital transformation, means that your enterprise has a wealth of new tools to create seamless communications for your employees and customers. 

However, there is a “but.”

With the benefits come new vulnerabilities for IP based attacks and the need to control communication streams as they cross your network boundaries. 

How can you protect your business and ensure that IP voice and video quality of experience is maximized? Find out by watching our webinar.

Irwin Lazar of Nemertes Research and Bryan Davies of Nokia explore:


	- Why IP communications is a key component of digital transformation 

	- The need to ensure security and privacy of voice and video – and how to do it
	- What the attack surfaces are for IP-based communications
	- What IPX is and how it impacts the future of business communications security
	- And more…
Enjoy!
{{my.Email Signature Person}}
{{my.Email Signature Title}}, Nokia
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; · Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; · Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
