<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18. TM forum event invitation.25397.Email 01</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Get more from your data--Meet us at TM Forum to learn how</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Meet with our experts
McKinsey says the average business is getting less than a third of the value they can from their data—Nokia can help you get more.
Are you on your way to your own digital transformation? Schedule a meeting with us &lt;[[mailto:catherine.bonanni@nokia.com?subject=RSVP]]&gt; at Digital Transformation World 2018 and find out how we can help you:



	- Personalize your customer care.
	- Overcome internal silos and reach decisions faster.
	- Innovate and monetize.


The “how” of your transformation starts with harnessing the power of connected intelligence. Come see what we are doing with our partners at the TM Forum Catalyst program:



	- Interconnecting businesses with application-aware network slices.
	- Maximizing engagement with predictive customer journeys.
	- Using AI in the cognitive contact center to improve the customer experience.
You can find Nokia on booth #300, Level 3 of the Acropolis Exhibition Center in Nice. Nokia speakers at the conference include:



	- Miikka Karhuluoma, Head of New Network Management Product Development, “Reimagining OSS/BSS”: Tuesday, May 15, 14.45 to 15.05
	- Andy Fruhling, VP Digital Experience &amp; Monetization Portfolio, Nokia Software,“AI and Data Analytics”: Wednesday, May 16, 14.55 to 15.40


Johan Vandenberghe, Bell Labs Consulting, Nokia, will be awarded the TM Forum Distinguished Fellowship during the VIP reception on the evening of Monday, May 14.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Karaportti 3, 02610 Espoo, Finland 
Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
