<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>2016Q3.Global.NUR.1962.PSTN.Email 4 - Insight article: Go holistic</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>The 4 essential ingredients of successful PSTN transformation</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
The four essential ingredients of a holistic PSTN transformation strategy
Question: what is the biggest challenge in a successful public switched telephone network (PSTN) transformation project?




	- Finding skilled workers


	- Maintaining forward progress


	- Managing stakeholders


	- Controlling execution


	- All of the above



If you answered e), give yourself a pat on the back! Making a success of PSTN transformation can only be done with a holistic approach that understands and overcomes these 4 key challenges. This approach recognizes that PSTN transformation goes way beyond the technical. It must align business strategy with regulatory considerations and, above all, ensure customers continue to get the quality of service they expect from you. 

Insight article: Go holistic to succeed with PSTN migration
In this article, learn more about the challenges and discover the 4 essential ingredients of a holistic PSTN transformation strategy. 




	- PSTN migration is a business challenge, not a technical upgrade


	- A holistic approach to migration optimizes OPEX, revenue, and efficiency


	- Migration requires the right plan, capabilities, execution, and partners



Read the article and for more information, don’t hesitate to contact our team &lt;[[mailto:Eveline.verschraegen@nokia.com]]&gt; or visit the Nokia PSTN Transformation &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/solutions/pstn-smart-transform]]&gt; website.
Connect with us
© 2016 Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
