<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokCorp.Partner.All.T.G.E.17038.Partner Newsletter October 2017.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Nokia Global Partner Program Newsletter for December</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Partner Newsletter December 2017
PROGRAM NEWS &lt;#programnews&gt; | FEATURED 
PRODUCT &lt;#featuredproduct&gt; | FEATURED SEGMENT &lt;#featuredsegment&gt; | SUCCESS STORIES &lt;#successstories&gt; | SURVEY &lt;#survey&gt; | TRAINING &lt;#tools&quot; style=&quot;color: #124191; font-size: 14px; font-style: normal; font-weight: bold; line-height: 150%;&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;TOOLS | EVENTS &lt;[[#events]]&gt;



Program News
During this holiday season…


Our thoughts turn sincerely to those who have made our progress possible. It is with much appreciation we say “Thank You” for your collaboration and partnership in helping Nokia deliver innovative technology solutions that connect the world. From our Company to yours, Happy Holidays and continued success for the coming year.










Featured Product
Optical Networking


Nokia’s optical networking portfolio supports next-generation multiservice and multilayer transport from access to core. It can help transform your customer’s traditional optical network into a more scalable, efficient, and flexible multilayer transport network that has the programmability and intelligence to rapidly address their service needs.








Explore Nokia Optical Networking &lt;[[https://networks.nokia.com/solutions/optical-networking]]&gt;

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;




Featured Segment
The Highway opportunity with the Nokia portfolio


If you are interested in selling or sell to highway agencies of Departments of Transportation, we encourage you to take a look at the following valuable resources and training which will assist you in your sales efforts.


	- Training, customer presentations, and customer collateral &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1507228752035]]&gt;
	- IP/MPLS Networks for Highways &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/?openFile=06941000002OnQZ]]&gt;
	- Intelligent Highways Brochure &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/?openFile=06941000002OnQP]]&gt;
	- Case Study England Highways &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/?openFile=06941000002OnPq]]&gt;
	- Highways Infographics &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/?openFile=06941000002OnPv]]&gt;


Technologies included in the Highways Solution: AirScale Wi-Fi, IP, Microwave, Optics, and Nokia Optical LAN.

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;




Success Stories
 &lt;#top&gt;
Nokia&apos;s optical transport technology to help Idea Cellular meet massive bandwidth demand


Nokia will help Idea Cellular meet ever-increasing bandwidth demand by deploying Nokia&apos;s 1830 Photonic Services Switch (PSS) based Wavelength Division Multiplexing (WDM) solution. The optical transport network solution will be implemented across fiber-constrained geographies on the Idea network. Once the technology is deployed, Idea will be able to provide high-bandwidth services to its subscribers.

Read press release &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/releases/2017/09/27/nokias-optical-transport-technology-to-help-idea-cellular-meet-massive-bandwidth-demand]]&gt;
Nokia 1830 Photonic Service Switch &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/1830-Photonic-Service-Switch]]&gt;
Watch video: Nokia PSE-2: The heart of the network for today and the future &lt;[[https://youtu.be/ZXkspNQwlaM]]&gt;


Nokia Optical LAN for your Healthcare customers


The proliferation of medical and non-medical applications brings new challenges for the “business as usual” approach of IT implementation in healthcare facilities. If your customer’s IT networks in these facilties are under increased pressure from patients, guests, physicians and devices demanding advanced connectivity, read the Digital Health Age article to learn more about a network solution for healthcare organizations. 

Read article &lt;[[http://digitalhealthage.com/passive-optical-lan-in-healthcare-and-the-need-for-proper-networks-in-hospitals/]]&gt;

Back to Top &lt;#top&gt;




Survey
Your voice is important!


As a reminder, please take our partner PRM Partner Portal survey before December 20 so we can capture your feedback to foster continual improvement. 

Take survey now &lt;[[https://www.surveymonkey.com/r/S7CVXK2]]&gt;

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;



Tools
Partner Portal


If you&apos;d like to receive regular notifications about updates to the Portal and its content, please join the public Chatter Group Portal Announcements. This group also allows users to post comments, suggestions, and requests, so you can let us know how the Portal can better serve your needs.

Join Chatter Group &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/group/0F941000000YClxCAG/portal-announcements]]&gt;

Pricing Catalog Updates

As a reminder, the following partner price catalog updates 
were recently updated and are now available on the Partner Portal.


	- Fixed Networks Nokia Optical LAN – MEA
	- Fixed Networks Nokia Optical LAN – Europe


To receive notifications on partner price catalog updates, please subscribe to Notifications in Partner Portal/Partner Personal space.

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;




Training
Training Catalog


A new Training Certification catalog is now available on the Partner Portal, in addition to course updates.


Access Training Certification catalog &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/06941000001uTBkAAM]]&gt;
Access Course updates  &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/068410000067PAi]]&gt;

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;




Marketing

Banners


Roll up banners are now available for you to use at events. Access from the Partner Portal after first logging into Salesforce.


	- IP Routing &lt;[[http://go.nokia.com/R00S009R0V003000W8ZDqU0]]&gt;
	- SDN Nuage Networks banner &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/ka241000000NdNEAA0/SDN-Nuage-Networks]]&gt;
	- Nokia Optical LAN banner &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/s/article/Passive-Optical-LAN]]&gt;










QR Codes
QR codes, or machine-readable optical labels, contain information about the item to which it is attached. Use these codes at your next event to drive customers to a website or landing page, or to marketing collateral that features the products and solutions you are showcasing.

Take a test drive by scanning the Nokia Optical LAN code below using a QR Reader app from your mobile. Or download various Nokia product QR Codes for your needs from the Partner Portal.









Download Nokia Optical LAN QR Codes &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/068410000046qcF]]&gt;
Download IP Routing QR Codes &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/068410000046qcj]]&gt;
Download 1830 PSS QR Codes &lt;[[https://www.partners.nokia.com/068410000046qdm]]&gt;

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;




Events
Nokia Partner Advisory Councils


The success of any partnership is ongoing dialogue. Business partnerships don’t thrive in a vacuum. Communications is essential to a mutually beneficial business relationship that allows both partners and Nokia to thrive in the market. It was with these thoughts in mind that led to successful Partner Advisory Council meetings in Rome, Italy and Nokia&apos;s Mountain View California facility.







PAC attendees hear from Nokia leadership to learn more about Nokia’s partner business, and ION partner strategy.

Back to Top &lt;[[#top]]&gt;
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
You are receiving this email because you&apos;ve subscribed to receive information from Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
