<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>19-1st to 5G-Strong First Steps-Email-em_s5Gw_stFsteps-T003LZ.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Webinar - Signaling in a 5G World</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Please join this webinar to learn about the relevance of signaling in 5G core networks.
As you plan and deploy 5G networks, you will also be preparing to implement new HTTP2 signaling technology inside the core and at the roaming edge. The 5G core network needs a signaling architecture that ensures security, reliability, and scalability. This webinar provides insights into 5G’s new service-based architecture (SBA), key building blocks to implement signaling control, use cases, the status of 3GPP standards, and deployment considerations.
Key discussion topics:


	- Examine signaling’s benefits
	- Deep dive into the importance of signaling control in 5G and signaling’s key use cases
	- Explore key deployment options and the current status of standards
	- Answer the audience&apos;s questions during live Q&amp;A


Speakers:


	- Diane Myers, Senior Research Director, VoIP, UC, and IMS, IHS Markit
	- Patrik Rokyta, Senior Director, Product Management, NetNumber
	- Satvinder Bawa, Senior Product Manager, Cloud Signaling Director, Nokia
	- Allen Tatara, Sr. Manager, Webinar Events, IHS Markit (Moderator)
Yours sincerely,
Nokia team
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[https://{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[https://{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[https://{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;




 &lt;[[https://{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;




 &lt;[[https://{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;




 &lt;[[https://{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;




 &lt;[[http://{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
