<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Cable-Service Provider-Email-AngaCom eDM-T0020H.Email reminder</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Don’t miss: Nokia at ANGA COM – Living the digital transformation</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Don’t miss out: Nokia at ANGA COM
Living the digital transformation 
12-14 June, 2018 Koelnmesse Hall 7, booth H11 Cologne, Germany 

 
Everyone is living the digital transformation. Users expect increasingly rich and intuitive experiences in an instant. To benefit from the imminent transition to 5G and the explosion of the IoT, your network needs to anticipate, adapt and respond automatically and instantaneously, as well as cost efficiently.

 
Join Nokia at ANGA COM 2018 to explore: 

 	- Delivering seamless connectivity in the gigabit era (with HFC, FTTH, optical transport, Wi-Fi and wireless) 
 	- Optimizing use of the cloud and network intelligence for improved performance and reduced OPEX (with analytics, IP Video, security and E2E cloud architectures) 
 	- Preparing for 5G (with cloud enabled packet cores and 5G-ready Anyhaul) 
 	- Providing new revenue-generating services (with private LTE, SD-WAN and Nokia Optical LAN) 

 Plan your booth visit today by booking a session or contacting directly your local sales representative.
Listen to our experts
Please look out for Nokia’s expert speakers in the conference talking about


	- Efficiencies brought by virtualization in cable access.
(Wednesday, 13 June, 11:45) 
	- Differentiating service experiences with IP network analytics. 
(Wednesday, 13 June, 15:00) 

	- Latest generation residential Wi-Fi mesh technologies. 
(Thursday, 14 June, 11:30) 

	- Raising the bar on SD-WAN with network orchestration. 
(Thursday, 14 June, 13:00) 




For further information about Nokia at ANGA COM, visit 
https://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/anga-com-2018 &lt;[[https://www.nokia.com/en_int/news/events/anga-com-2018?did=d000000000fk&amp;utm_campaign=cable_transformation&amp;utm_source=email-list-selected-cable-accounts_reminder&amp;utm_medium=email&amp;utm_content=reminder-email]]&gt;

If you have any questions, please do not hesitate to reach out to your local sales representative. 

We are looking forward to welcoming you at our booth, 
Your Nokia team
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Karaportti 3, 02610 Espoo, Finland 
Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia’s networks business or its third-party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
