<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-Util Crit Comms-Util Architecture-Email-UTC Dec5 invite-T002G9.Email</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Variable frequency control webinar December 5, 2018</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Efficient and resilient future grids

Join us and hear what Dr. Steven Blair has to share about a new method of decentralized frequency control
December 5, 2018 at 8am PST | 10am CST | 11am EDT
Nokia’s partnership between the Energy Innovation Center and the University of Strathclyde, utilizing a Nokia SD-WAN to link multiple laboratories in real-time, has tested a new method of decentralized frequency control. This ability to rapidly balance the grid is key for integrating vast numbers of controllable, renewable generators and other resources. The fast-acting response – enhanced through new measurements and communications systems– is also critical for addressing the challenges associated with low-inertia power systems.
The webinar will explain how this solution has been demonstrated, and how this can help enable efficient and resilient future grids.
Speaker:
Dr. Steven Blair
Lecturer, University of Strathclyde
Dr. Steven Blair holds the Nokia Lectureship at the University of Strathclyde, Glasgow, UK. He received the MEng degree in Computer and Electronic Systems in 2008, and the PhD degree in Electrical Engineering in 2013, both from the University of Strathclyde. His research interests include power system protection, communications, power quality, phasor measurement units, and real-time simulation. He is a member of IEC Technical Committee 57 Working Group 10 and CIGRE Working Group B5.64.
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia.

 Nokia: Karaportti 3, 2610 Espoo, Finland
 Contact Us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
&lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Twitter}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Linkedin}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Facebook}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Youtube}}]]&gt;     &lt;[[{{my.SocialURL-Blog}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia Networks or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
