<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <description>17-BG-SSE-Email-HoNE IHS report-T001P4</description>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.ComColl.SDP.none.N.G.N.14762.SDP Pilot campaign.SSE_ENG_5_IHS_Report</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Analyst shows how to securely scale your network</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
IHS Markit expert talks Secure Service Enablement
A key concern for today’s network engineers is how the move to IP Multimedia Subsystem (IMS) and Voice over Long-Term Evolution (VoLTE) infrastructures will impact the network’s security, performance, and reliability. At the same time, communications service providers (CSPs) must balance profitability and agility for the future.

 In this report, Diane Myers from IHS Markit explores:


	- Key market trends for VoLTE, IMS, roaming and service enablement
	- How to securely increase network performance, reliability and profitability
	- How to gain agility for the future
	- Lessons for tier 2-4 operators to learn from tier 1 deployments


Discover the power of Nokia Secure Service Enablement
 Bringing together our virtualized Session Border Controller (SBC), Cloud Signaling Director (CSD) and Authentication, Authorization and Accounting (AAA), Secure Service Enablement delivers what you need to secure your infrastructure, boost performance and reliability, and ensure your network stays profitable and agile for tomorrow.
Enjoy! 
Brendan Ziolo 
Head of Secure Service Enablement Marketing, Nokia
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia’s networks business or its third-party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
