<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokCorp.Partner.All.D.G.E.19007. LightSpeed co-branded newsletter delivery 1.</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Bringing broadband within your community’s reach just got easier</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Bringing broadband within your community&apos;s reach just got easier 
Dear {{lead.Full Name:default=Sir/Madame}}, 
 
In today’s major metropolitan areas, broadband internet access drives commerce, supports superior education and healthcare, builds economic prosperity, and enhances quality of life. However, smaller municipalities and rural areas that struggle with aging communications technology face being left behind. 
 
It is now time to consider a broadband fiber solution that lets utilities extend gigabit internet access services to underserved areas. Broadband fiber also provides utilities with the communications foundation to make their distribution grid smarter, more reliable and capable of integrating renewable generation and storage sources, while cutting demand peaks and thereby reducing supply costs. 
 
LightSpeed Technologies was recently named Nokia’s #1 Business Partner, specializing in broadband/FTTx networking solutions. Since 2001 LightSpeed has been assisting utilities and municipalities with initial systems engineering, material management, product Installation and system testing and turn-up as well as on-going maintenance support. We welcome the opportunity to demonstrate to your organization our renowned customer service and technical assistance. 
 
To find out more about Nokia’s proven end-to-end FTTH solution and how you can enable your local citizens and businesses to join a group of the world’s most connected communities, download the Utility Broadband brochure.
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
