<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>18-GEPS TO-Partner-Email-Accreditation EDM-T001ZW.Email - 30Day DIS NAM</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Accreditation deadline approaching</subject>
    <textOnly>View as web page &lt;[[{{system.viewAsWebpageLink}}]]&gt;
Accreditation deadline approaching
Dear Partner, 

 I am emailing to remind you again that the deadline of June 17, 2018 is approaching for your company to meet all criteria for Partner Program Product Accreditation at your current level. You will want to pay attention to this deadline if you wish to continue the rights and entitlements afforded to you as a result of your Program Accreditation tier, such as pricing discounts.

 As a reminder, Nokia requires any partner who was contracted under Nokia Distributor program PPA-DIS as of September 17, 2017, and who has committed to become Product Accredited at the Premier 
tier, to meet all the published criteria to fully achieve and/or maintain that Accreditation tier. Detailed Program Rules relating to Accreditation may be found in the Partner Portal in Sections 5.5 a and b of the Distributor Program Rules. A brief list of the requirements by tier and product can be found below.

 You may always find your current accreditation level by visiting your Account in the Nokia Partner Portal. Simply: Log in &gt; Click on Accounts Tab &gt; Select Account Name &gt; Select Related Tab &gt; Scroll to your Accreditations Table. 

 If you have any questions related to this upcoming deadline or your current accreditation status, please contact your Partner Sales Manager.

 Regards,

 Jerome Jullien
Vice President, Nokia Global Partner Program
Accreditation and associated Certification Requirements
 3.0 Distributor September 2017
 NAM
 IP Networking, Optical Networking, Fixed Networks, and Nokia Optical LAN 








Base


Premier




Co-signed current PPA contract


✓


✓




Jointly approved Business Plan in Partner Portal






✓




Certified Staff:
IP Networking, Optical Networking, Fixed Networks, or Nokia Optical LAN

(1) Sales Associate &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489534428476]]&gt;
(2) Sales Associates &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489534428476]]&gt;




(2) Sales Engineer Specialists &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489534441122]]&gt;




(1) Field Technician &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489534477892]]&gt; (Optional)




(1) Network Integration Engineer &lt;[[http://learningstore.nokia.com/partner/#?item=n.1489534488438]]&gt; (Optional)



Partner demonstration / lab capabilities






Optional





*For specific Product Line Specializations (e.g. Mobile Networks, Application &amp; Analytics) Nokia may require additional Certifications. Such adjusted Accreditation Requirements will be communicated to the affected Partners separately.
Connect with us
©{{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia | Contact us &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/contact]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[http://company.nokia.com/en/privacy]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt;
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
