<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<EmailTemplate xmlns="http://soap.sforce.com/2006/04/metadata">
    <available>true</available>
    <encodingKey>UTF-8</encodingKey>
    <name>17.NokiCorp.Cable.18966.Cable-BPM survey - eDM to clients.03 Email DE w/o Sales</name>
    <style>none</style>
    <subject>Your opinion of Nokia</subject>
    <textOnly>${preheader}
Your opinion of Nokia
Dear {{lead.Salutation:default=edit me}} {{lead.Last Name:default=edit me}}, 

We&apos;re emailing to let you know about a short survey that Nokia would like to invite you to take part in. In return for your participation, a donation of $30 (or the equivalent in local currency) will be made to a charity that you will be able to select on completion of the survey.

We are interested to understand your opinion of our cable operator products and services and how you think we might improve them. The survey will include questions about Nokia and other brands so you’ll be able to provide feedback on the industry as a whole.

The survey will be conducted by an independent third party and should take around 10 minutes. All opinions you offer will remain anonymous and confidential. The results will be used, in aggregate, to improve Nokia’s products and services and the way we work with our customers overall. 

This week you will receive a message from Nokia@Intellisurvey.com with the subject line ‘Nokia invites you to share your opinion’ and a link to participate in the survey. 

Thank you in advance for your participation. We value your opinion. 

Nokia Customer Marketing Team


If you would prefer to not take part in the research please email &lt;news.networks@nokia.com &lt;[[mailto:news.networks@nokia.com]]&gt;&gt;
Connect with us
© {{my.CopyrightYear}} Nokia. Contact us &lt;[[{{my.ContactUs}}]]&gt; | Privacy policy &lt;[[{{my.PrivacyPolicy}}]]&gt; | Unsubscribe &lt;[[{{system.unsubscribeLink}}]]&gt; 
This message has been sent to you because of your relationship with Nokia or its third party licensors who are trusted partners of Nokia.</textOnly>
    <type>custom</type>
    <uiType>Aloha</uiType>
</EmailTemplate>
